and
e
[Music]
[Música]
what I thought that loving no longer
lo que pensé que eso de amar ya no
existed that kisses are given away on
existía que los besos se regalan en
any
cualquier
corner I thought that loving
esquina Yo que pensé que eso de amar
was just a game but I look at you and I'm
solo era un juego pero te miro y es que
dying to
muero por
have you you with me to invest my life in
tenerte tu a mig invertir mi vida en
exciting you and
ilusionarte y
I will win the game the time that is
yo ganaré la partida el tiempo que se
[Music]
[Música]
lost asking for the day that your soul is
perdió pidada día que tu alma se a mi
mine until the last kiss that says goodbye to
Lía hasta el último beso que despida
this path and I ask every day to always be able to
esta vía y pido cada día siempre poder
love you waiting for the moment to have you I praise myself
amarte esperando el momento de tenerte
if the world separates I'll stay
loé si el mundo se separa me quedo
with you if tomorrow doesn't dawn I'll stay
contigo si mañana no amanece me quedo
with you if you want me to stay I'll
contigo si tú quieres que me quede me
stay with you
quedo
what do things matter to me and
contigo qué me importan las cosas y
when I smile I turn around I'm with you with
cuando sonrío me doy media vuelta estoy
you investing my life in
contigo invertir mi vida en
exciting you and
ilusionarte y
[Music]
[Música]
I will win the game the time that is
yo ganaré la partida el tiempo que se
lost asking for you Every day that your soul be
perdió te pido Cada día que tu alma sea
my guide until the last kiss that says goodbye to
mi guía hasta el último beso que despida
this path and I ask every day to always be able to
esta vía y pido cada día siempre poder
love you waiting for the moment to have you I
amarte esperando el momento de tenerte
will
yo adelante
[Music]
[Música]
invest my  life
invertir mi vida
excite you and
ilusionarte y
[Music]
[Música]
I will win the game the time that was
yo ganaré la parti el tiempo que se
lost and I ask Every day that you
perdió y pido Cada día que tu
[Music]
[Música]
you kiss
ú bes
despa
despa
yid [ __ ] man I have to buy an arm
yid [__] tío tengo que comprar un brazo
man I have to buy an arm for this
tío tengo que comprar un brazo para esto
man I'm not buying it because Perea is let's see
tío no lo compro por Perea está a ver
the camera goes out of focus I'm going to touch it
que la cámara se desenfoca voy a tocarla
that it is that
que está que
coo that is not the word it's
se coo que no es la palabra que está
expired no Ah well no it doesn't have to go
vencido no Ah pues no no se tiene que
out of focus because it's expired man the arm
desenfocar que está vencido tío el brazo
and the mic falls you see it falls
y se cae el micro lo ves se cae para
down you see look I want it Put it here
abajo lo veis mira lo quiero Pon aquí
and it goes down because it's expired I
hace y se va abajo porque está vencido
have to buy a new one and it's laziness
tengo comprar un nuevo y es pereza
look at you that
fíjate tú que eso
eh look at you that it's not worth much not
eh fíjate tú que que no vale mucho ni
even no well How are you family
siquiera no bueno Qué tal estáis familia
How have you been Well today I gave an
Cómo habéis estado Bueno hoy he dado una
exclusive at the salsería quite
exclusiva en la salsería bastante
powerful and funny the truth is it makes me
potente y divertida la verdad me hace
laugh a lot how time always puts
mucha gracia como el tiempo pone siempre
everything in its place okay And I think that
todo en su sitio vale Y creo que se
more things are coming I think that tomorrow
vienen más cosas creo que además mañana
yes I think that tomorrow maybe we have
sí creo que además mañana a lo mejor
another one I think that maybe tomorrow  we
tenemos otra creo que a lo mejor mañana
have another the members is
tenemos otra los miembros me está
telling me Pili to see them let
diciendo Pili que los vea a ver un
me go for a moment because today we have today we have
dejarme porque hoy tenemos hoy tenemos
a big live broadcast in the main main
un directo gordo en el princi principal
with Trium and with Tuyupa that we just
con trium y con tuyupa que acabamos de
had the
tener acaba de llegar la sentencia
full sentence of the Daniel
completa del caso Daniel
Sancho case just arrived the full sentence okay
Sancho la sentencia completa vale
Lilit eye the full sentence eh let's
lilit ojo la sentencia completa eh vamos
see what we find I was
a ver qué nos encontramos estaba
talking to Trium now While
hablando con trium ahora Mientras que
the live broadcast was starting and at the moment there isn't a
iniciaba el directo y de momento pues no
big deal in the sense that there is
hay la gran cosa en el sentido de que
something that we didn't know
algo que no supiéramos
but Trium is translating I don't know
pero está ah traduciendo la trium no sé
if Tuyupa might have found
si tuyupa a lo mejor habrá encontrado
something else Because Tuyupa has it a little
algo más Porque tuyupa lo tiene un poco
faster maybe to translate
más más rápido a lo mejor para traducir
and let's go Triun is there leaving his
y vamos triun está ahí dejándose los
balls in Translating like this
[__] en Traducir así
[Music]
[Música]
so well we'll see
que así que bueno ya veremos
later 14 members 1404 members I think that
luego 14 miembros 1404 miembros creo que
those from yesterday have joined right
noos han sumado los de ayer verdad
Because yesterday around here there was quite a
Porque ayer por aquí hubo hubo bastante
rain of members no first of all I
lluvia de de miembros no en primer lugar
wanted to
quería
dedicate a few words and my condolences to the
dedicar unas palabras y el pésame a la
family of this man
familia de de este hombre
winner of the house of your life okay He
ganador de la casa de tu vida vale Ha
passed away at the
fallecido a los
age of 44 man  There is no right in this life
44 años tío No hay derecho en esta vida
that anyone should go at 44 years old and
de que nadie se vaya con est 44 años y
I understand Eh triu tells me that he has
tengo entendido Eh triu me habla que ha
found something new Tri tells me that he has
encontrado algo nuevo Tri me habla que
found something
ha encontrado algo
new but I'm not going to tell you I'm going to
nuevo pero no os lo voy a decir voy a
read the message but I'm not going to
leer el mensaje pero no os lo voy a
tell you I'm going to tell you later juanma had
decir os lo voy a decir luego juanma fue
a stomach reduction operation he
operado de una reducción de estómago
lost 60 kg after that
perdió 60 kg tras esa
operation his stomach stuck to the
intervención el estómago se pegó a la
mesh that they put in and it had created
malla que me pusieron y me había creado
a hole he had a
un boquete tenía tenía un infección de
horse
caballo sea Esto fue algo de salud que
infection be it This was something health-related that happened to him but of course I understand this was many years ago because I met him well in the house of your life he was already thin he was already thin he was very fat I would say much more than in this photo I would say
mucho más que en esta foto Yo diría que
much more than in that photo
mucho más que en esa foto
and and here he was del gillo Here he was
y y aquí estaba del gillo Aquí estaba
del gillo very nice the truth is the guy
del gillo muy Majo la verdad el chava
very nice very nice but [ __ ] what a
muy Majo muy simpático pero [__] qué
stick no at 44 years old nobody should leave
palo no con 44 años no se debería ir
but I think that still not
nadie pero creo que todavía no
[Music] they do
[Música]
n't know it's the cause of
saben no saben es la causa de la de la
death okay they do
muerte vale
n't know the house of the cause of
no saben la casa de la la causa de la
death  then over here zelin has
muerte luego por aquí zelin le ha
dedicated a
dedicado un
tweet he says with much pain we say goodbye
tweet dice con mucho dolor decimos adiós
to juanma garcia winner of the first
a juanma García ganador de la primera
edition of the house of your life and a great
edición de la casa de tu vida y un gran
lgtb iq Plus reference on television
referente lgtb iq Plus en televisión
rest in peace friend Well
descansa en paz amigo Bueno pues ya ves
you see, of course man, of course yes
tú pues claro hombre pues claro que sí
eh from so many years ago Well yes This
eh de tantos años que hace Pues sí Este
was his partner this boy who came
era su pareja este muchacho que venía
with him was his partner I think
con él era su pareja creo
and and there we were at the posada de las
y y ahí estábamos en la posada de las
animas the truth is We were there at the
animas la verdad Ahí estuvimos en la
posada de las animas I don't remember what
posada de las animas No me acuerdo qué
I was doing there back then but
hacía yo ahí en aquel entonces pero
come on this is old eh these photos
vamos esto es Antiguo eh estas fotos
I'm talking about that they were broadcasting
estoy hablando de que estaban emitiendo
the house of your life also when I
la casa de tu vida además cuando he
looked for that photo I found others that that that that that
buscado esa foto he encontrado otras
we are with
que que que que que estamos nosotros con
more people from the house of your life with
más gente de la casa de tu vida con
Vanessa David I
Vanessa David
liked David a lot those people were
David me cayó muy bien esa gente eran
citano if I'm not mistaken not Vanessa
citano si no me equivoco no Vanessa
Vanessa and David I don't remember but I
Vanessa y David no me acuerdo pero David
remember that I liked David a lot the one that
me acuerdo que me cayó muy bien la que
I liked so much was not the girlfriend but
me caía regular era la no la novia sino
the previous girlfriend because
la anterior novia porque es que
David David was with another David entered
David David estaba con otra David entró
with another couple in another reality show And
con otra pareja en otro reality Y
then
entonces
eh  he fell in love with Vanessa and left his
eh Se enamoró de Vanessa y dejó a la
girlfriend to go with Vanessa and
parienta por por irse con Vanessa y ya
with Vanessa it lasted many years and I think
con Vanessa duró muchos años que creo
that to this day they are probably still together
que a día de hoy seguramente seguirán
but no no his partner was the one in the other
pero no no su pareja era la de la otra
photo No man the one in the other photo the one in
foto No hombre la de la otra foto la de
the magazine was the couple from the reality show
la revista era la pareja del reality
But he already When he entered again in in that
Pero él ya Cuando entró de nuevo en en
in that other reality show
en ese en ese otro reality
well the house of your life it was not it would be
bueno la casa de tu vida no era sería
Big Brother the reunion or something like that I mean that That one
gran hermano el reencuentro o algo así O
apart doesn't win this photo
sea esa Esa esa aparte no gana esta foto
that I have shown you that I have already closed
que os he enseñado que ya la he cerrado
that photo that I showed you was not from the
esa foto que os enseñado no era de la
house of your life That that photo that I have
casa de tu vida Esa esa foto que os he
shown you of me with him well there is
enseñado que estoy yo con él bueno está
Lorena with him at the Posada de las Animas
Lorena con él en la posada de las animas
that that was not the house of your life they were
eso eso no era la casa de tu vida eran
contestants from the house of your life But
concursantes de la casa de tu vida Pero
that was a reunion also there was
eso era un reencuentro además ahí fue
uh Chiqui
eh Chiqui
Martín to Sara I think she is also I don't
Martín a Sara creo que también está no
remember but a lot of a lot
me acuerdo pero un montón de un montón
of I don't know if it was a Big Brother
de Es que no sé si era un gran hermano
reunion what was it okay then on the
reencuentro qué es lo que era vale luego
other hand well we also had
por otro lado pues también hemos tenido
the news today that  Julian
hoy la noticia de que Julián
Muñoz speaks tomorrow on Friday I
Muñoz habla mañana en de viernes Yo
have one thing Okay and it's that today we're not
tengo una cosa Vale y Es que hoy pues no
going to be able to upload the
vamos a poder subir tampoco el vídeo de
Big Brother video either, just like we
gran hermano al igual que él tampoco lo
couldn't upload it on
pudimos subir el
Tuesday. This is what happens when you have
martes Esto es lo que pasa cuando tienes
three channels, okay, today I ca
tres canales vale hoy el vídeo de gran
n't upload the Big Brother video because I
hermano no lo puedo subir porque no
can't watch Big Brother today the gala,
puedo ver gran hermano hoy la gala por
why? Because at 10:30 I have a live show with
qué Porque a las 10:30 tengo directo con
Tri with your yupa, so uh when I
Tri con con tu yupa entonces eh cuando
know when things clash. Well, you
se cuando se chocan las cosas Pues tú
have to prioritize the one that works best,
tienes que priorizar la que más funciona
the one that suits you best, of course, obviously not. So
la que más te va claro evidentemente no
today,
entonces hoy
uh, today what I'm going to do is go live
eh hoy lo que yo voy a hacer es directo
on the
en el canal
main channel and maybe if I finish
principal y a lo mejor si termino
early and there's something important for the
temprano y hay algo importante para la
salsería, maybe I'll go there,
salsería a lo mejor me voy para allá
but I think there's not going to be anything
pero creo que no va a haber nada
important. Okay, I'll leave for the salsería
importante vale a la salsería me iré
tomorrow at more or less the same time as today
mañana más o menos la misma hora que hoy
to probably give another exclusive, but the thing is that
para dar otra exclusiva seguramente pero
when you
lo que tiene es eso que que cuando
have several channels, well, of course you can't
tienes varios canales Pues claro no
do everything 100% for None of
puedes hacer todo al 100% de Ninguno de
the three, for None of the three, why?
los tres de Ninguno de los tres por qué
Well, because you don't watch one channel today, today, the
Pues porque no mira un canal hoy hoy lo
ideal thing  it would have been your newscast on
ideal hubiera sido su noticiero en
telesalseo your newscast at the salsería your your
telesalseo su noticiero en la salsería
live broadcast at the salsería your live broadcast
su su directo en la salsería su directo
on telesalseo okay eh your Big
en telesalseo vale eh su vídeo de gran
Brother video before the SEO but of course
hermano entes al seo pero claro es que
then eh I can't make the video that I
entonces eh No puedo hacer el vídeo que
made on the main channel which has
he hecho en el canal principal que ha
been very interesting the video that I
estado muy interesante el vídeo que
just published is missing the thumbnail I have
acabo de publicar le falta la miniatura
seen yet
he visto todavía
and the live broadcast tonight of Teresa
e y el directo esta noche de Teresa
Alceo I think that it is more important than
alceo Yo creo que es más importante que
commenting on the gr gala is that you can't
que comentar la gala de gr es que no
do everything you can't do everything that
puedes hacer todo no puedes hacer todo
is the problem in quote marks that
ese es el problema entre comillas que
I
que yo
have if I
tengo si yo
only have one channel and one theme we
tengo Solamente un canal y una temática
break it but of course we have to
rompemos pero claro tenemos que ir
move between the three So I
moviéndonos entre las tres Entonces yo
think that between commenting on the gala of watching
creo que entre comentar la gala de ver
the brother gala and commenting on the
la gala de hermano y comentarla el vídeo
Big Brother video, well I think that
de gran hermano pues yo creo que a la
people are more interested in the complete sentence to
gente le interesa más la sentencia a
Daniel Sancho that we are going to
Daniel Sancho completa que la vamos a
give it
dar en
exclusively we are going to give it exclusively that's
exclusiva la vamos a dar en exclusiva es
what there is well Julian
lo que hay bueno Julian
Muñoz I love that this man in the
Muñoz me flipa que este hombre en el
state that he is in that he is
estado en el que
hyper
está que está hiper
mega hyper mega hyper mega hyper mega
mega hiper mega hiper mega hiper mega
yamal
yamal
vale is still sitting on a
vale se esté sentando todavía en un
heart program I mean what does he
programa del corazón O sea qué es lo que
want to give my step through the life of that
quiere dar mi paso por la vida de esa
lady was
señora fue
disastrous again he's going to talk about
nefasto otra vez va a hablar de la
Pantoja but if he already gave one he made
Pantoja pero si él ya dio una él hizo
a docuseries do you remember that after
una docuserie os acordáis que después de
after the documentary about Rocío Carrasco
después del documental de Rocío Carrasco
a
se hizo una
docuseries was made But why does he want
docuserie Pero para qué quiere
money why does he want money to
dinero para qué quiere dinero para
leave it to his heirs I just don't
dejarlo a sus Herederos Es que no
understand But he made a docuseries
entiendo Pero él se hizo una docuserie
don't you
no os
remember I have not been happy with that
acordáis yo no he sido feliz con esa
person I do not have good memories she
persona no guardo buen recuerdo ella se
has worried No now son no longer
ha preocupado No ya hijo ya ya no hace
need to say it Javi a lot and well there is no
falta que lo diga Javi mucho y bien no
one who Never leave your main channel No I am not going to leave None of the four channels in fact what I would like here in telesalseo I would love for telesalseo to work like the salsería or in other words the excerpts to be uploaded here not in la
extractos subirlos aquí no en la
piruleta in la piruleta the excerpts
piruleta en la piruleta los extractos
are triumphing Well basically I think it
están triunfando Pues básicamente creo
has How many millions of visits
que tiene Cuántos millones de visitas
well millions of visits almost a million
bueno millones de visitas casi el millón
visits has the  lollipop a month no
de visit tiene la piruleta al mes no
Lili 700,000 has had this last month
Lili 700.000 ha tenido este último mes
damn I would love to add this to
[__] a mí me encantaría esto sumarlo a
telesalseo no and what and that in
telesalseo no y que y que en el propio
telesalseo itself they would upload apart from the
telesalseo se subieran aparte de los
newscasts and me doing live shows
noticieros y de que yo haga directos
okay because the excerpts too like in
vale pores los extractos también como en
the salsería in the salsería the
la salsería en la salsería se suben los
newscasts are uploaded they upload the
noticieros se suben los se hacen los
live shows and the excerpts are uploaded and
directos y se suben los extracto y no
nothing happens but here people don't
pasa nada pero aquí la gente no se lo
take it well so you can see what the
toma bien para que veáis lo que son los
channels are like each one is different and and
canales que cada uno es diferente y y
each one you know how it works each audience
cada uno sabes funciona cada audiencia
reacts in a way to things and
reacciona de una manera a las cosas y yo
here many times I have tried to upload the
aquí muchas veces he intentado subir los
excerpts after the live shows and
extractos después de los directo y la
people complain the visits drop a lot
gente se queja las visitas bajan mucho
anyway so well now
en fin así que bueno ahora ahora están
things are going very well Now now we only
las cosas muy bien Ahora ahora solamente
need our
nos falta nuestra
Marina okay she sent me a photo of the
Marina vale que me ha mandado una foto
ass that she was with her right now
al asne de que estaba con ella ahora
at this moment the fourth channel
mismo en estos momentos el cuarto canal
Raquel It's the lollipop that
Raquel Es la piruleta que se suben
videos that we get from here from the
vídeos que sacamos de aquí de los
live shows this month is slower but yes you
directos este mes más flojo pero sí te
go 15  times of course Yes yes it's that
me vas 15 veces claro Sí sí es que dar
realizing that this has been August eh Lili it has
cuenta que está ha sido agosto eh Lili
n't gone bad eh We can't complain
no ha ido mal eh No nos podemos quejar
I think that September is going to be one of the
yo creo que septiembre va a ser uno de
best Javi son yesterday you went too far
mejores Javi hijo ayer te pasaste
with me eh Why pains What
conmigo eh Por qué dolores Qué te ha
happened to you what happened to you pains
pasado qué te ha pasado dolores
Tell me we are very whiny Yes yes the
Cuéntamelo somos muy quejicas Sí sí la
truth is that the ladies are very whiny
verdad que las señoras son muy quejicas
but but you are very whiny the lady
pero pero sois muy quejicas la señora
eh I complain little eh I complain little I
eh poco me quejo eh poco me quejo me
put on radio mode that I'm going to take the
pongo en modo radio que voy a [__] el
car to go to work give you all a
coche para ir a trabajar daros todos por
greeting very well bell You say
saludado muy bien campanilla Tú di que
yes to [ __ ] off people now everyone
sí a tomar por culo la gente ya todo el
wants a greeting one by one what I
mundo quiere un saludo uno por uno qué
tell you what I tell you for your health he
te digo qué Te digo por tu salud ni se
hasn't even worried and I don't give a damn he hasn't worried and I don't give a damn It's that
ha preocupado y tres [__] me
I
[__] me importan Es que yo este
don't see this man sticking there eh I this
hombre no veo que pegue ahí eh yo este
man I I don't see them hitting I mean they
hombre yo yo no veo que peguen o sea
were like he was like they were like
estaban como estaba como estaban como
trying to protect him not super
intentando protegerlo no super
protect him at the door of the
protegerlo en la puerta de la de la
clinic yes you told me you told me something
clínica sí me dijiste al me dijiste algo
what  I feel like it or something like that I don't
lo que me de la gana o algo así no me
remember well I say [ __ ] How angry
acuerdo bien digo [__] Cómo se enfada
Javi dolores dolores gets I told you I
Javi dolores dolores te dije
told you that because you came to tell me
te dije eso porque tú viniste a decirme
that if I'm going to do the whole live
que si me voy a hacer todo el directo
Antonio David and I told you well I do what
Antonio David y te dije pues hago lo que
I want but come on it's not what I want I do
me dé la gana pero vamos no es lo que me
n't rule the channel I don't rule
dé la gana Yo no mando en el canal Yo no
you rule but of course I don't
mando mandáis ustedes pero claro Yo no
rule you rule the topics that are there look today we're
mando mandan los temas que haya mira hoy
not going to do a live Antonio
no nos vamos a hacer un directo Antonio
David dolores but today you don't come to me
David dolores pero hoy no me vienes a mí
to tell me are you going to do a live of
a decirme te vas a hacer un directo de
Julián that you're in love Antonia David
Julián que estás enamorado Antonia David
don't you find me more
no te parezco yo más
handsome I ask will I last a little
guapo pregunto te voy a durar un poco
longer I'm 10 years younger What's up Sister
más tengo 10 años menos Qué pasa Sor
Cotilla Although you never know because I
Cotilla Aunque nunca se sabe porque
'm crazy but why do you
estoy dcho una [__] pero para que
bring Julián if he can't even speak
llevan a Julián si no puede ni hablar
because man let's see the truth I the
pues porque hombre a ver la verdad yo la
truth matters to you Julián Muñoz what he's
verdad a ustedes importa Julián Muñoz lo
going to say was a joke man no no it
que vaya a decir era broma hombre no no
wasn't a joke dolores don't back off don't back off it
era broma dolores no recule no recule no
wasn't a joke it wasn't you're going to seem all like that to the
era broma no era te va a parecer tod al
other now no no no I didn't do it it was a
otro ahora no no no lo he hecho era
joke no no no no  back down you
broma no no no no recules me lo dijiste
really told me do you care what
de verdad a ustedes os importa lo que
Julian says my Julian spoke to me Julian
diga Julián mi Julián me habló Julián
Contrera spoke to me Julian Contreras didn't
Contrera me habló Julián Contreras no le
answer the message man my
contestado al mensaje tío tengo la
head is
cabeza
terrible my head is terrible It's that I can't
fatal tengo la cabeza fatal Es que no
man It's that I
puedo tío Es que yo me
get up okay babe I listen to it I'm
levanto vale churrita Lo escucho estoy
live now and from here I
en directo ahora y de aquí me voy
run to the Principal I listen to it later
corriendo al Principal lo escucho luego
okay I don't forget I have it
vale no se me olvida lo tengo aquí
written down here I have it written down here I
apuntado lo tengo aquí apuntado lo he
said it and I get up in the
dicho y yo es que me me levanto por la
morning and I have 28 WhatsApp it always never
mañana y tengo 28 WhatsApp siempre no
fails I get up in the morning I have 28
falla me levanto por la maana tengo 28
WhatsApp everyone wants to talk to me
WhatsApp todo el mundo quiere hablarme
everyone wants to tell me something okay that's
todo el mundo quiere contarme algo vale
WhatsApp that's WhatsApp okay I mean
eso es WhatsApp eso es WhatsApp vale o
that's WhatsApp and of course I try to
sea eso es WhatsApp y y claro intento
answer what I'm seeing you know
contestar lo que yo voy viendo sabes
but there are many times they keep downloading
pero hay muchas veces se me van bajando
and it just occurs to me that
y se me acaba de venir a la cabeza que
Julian was talking to me and I didn't open it And it
Julián me estaba hablando y no lo abrí Y
will probably be to send me some
seguramente será para mandarme alguna
powerful information
información potente
I liked him better before than now you're boring
me gustaba más antes que ahora aburres
Maria del Carmen but if possible I'm
Maria del Carmen pero si cabe estoy
better off my step you guys care what
mejor mi paso a ustedes importa lo que
say Julian
diga Julián
Muñoz I mean because here in this program
Muñoz o sea porque aquí en este programa
they pay A lot of
pagan Una
money here in this program they pay A lot of
pasta aquí en este programa pagan Una
money
pasta
and they pay it to have people who don't
y la pagan para para tener gente que no
usually accept not to sit on these
suelen aceptar no sentarse en estos
programs but tomorrow Julian Muñoz goes Maite
program pero es que mañana van Julián
Maite Maite Galdeano not saldivar
Maite Maite Maite galdeano no saldivar
Maite
Maite
Galdeano and Kiko Jiménez I don't know if they
galdeano y Kiko Jiménez Que no sé si los
put them I didn't understand very well if they are going
pone no he entendido muy bien si los van
to put them face to face man if they put them
a poner cara a cara hombre si lo ponen
face to face they could give us a
cara a cara puede darnos un programita
nice little program but separately again the
guapo pero por separados otra vez la
truth
verdad
Javi did you find out about Chabelita who
Javi te has enterado lo de Chabelita el
is
que es
Jessica Julia Muñoz married Maite
Jessica juliá Muñoz se casó con Maite
right she married Maite Although Maite
verdad se casó con Maite Aunque Maite
has a
tiene
boyfriend but I think it's because it's for
novio pero creo que por será por
some reason or whatever I don't know I do
algún para querede o yo que sé no tengo
n't know it's for I don't know the truth he
ni idea no sé será para no sé la verdad
will have his reason and we don't know I don't know
tendrá su motivo y no lo sabemos no sé
if someone came to
si alguien llego a
explain it to me I am interested sero
explicarlo a mí me interesa sero
patatero I am that the truth uh
patatero Yo es que la verdad eh
that Julian Muñoz has already given many
que Julián Muñoz ya ha dado muchas
interviews it is not
entrevistas no es actualidad
even current events the only thing that
siquiera lo único que estaba haciendo
Julian Muñoz was doing news for the issue of the
noticias julan Muñoz por el tema del
state of his  health what a man who is
estado de su salud que hombre que está
delicate and what a man who is how he is
delicado y que hombre que está como está
Well in fact there were many headlines already
Bueno de hecho había muchos titulares ya
of people who thought he was
de gente que lo daba por
dead you know what I'm telling you
muerto sabes lo que te digo
then but current events his his he this
entonces pero actualidad su su he esto
as
como
such I don't see much
tal No le veo mucha
substance what's
chicha qué
going on don't
pasa no me
tell me a pendic
diga un pendic
City the
City la
poor thing That hurts like all your [ __ ] mother
pobre Eso duele como tod su [__] madre
they say
dicen
no Elena What's
no Elena Qué
going on mm
pasa mm
H has found that
H me ha encontrado eso
Lili
Lili
Ah Julian answers me
Ah me contesta Julian
eh Aida Anizar attacked while covering
eh Aida anizar agredida mientras cubría
the conflict of
el conflicto de la vivienda ocupada de
Manu
Manu
Tenorio's occupied housing regarding the issue of
Tenorio respecto al tema de la vivienda
Manu Tenorio's
de Manu Tenorio
occupied housing I have been seeing some
ocupada he estado viendo algú unos t un
somewhat regrettable eh of people rejoicing
poco lamentables eh de gente alegrándose
that Manu Tenorio
que Manu Tenorio
as he is right-wing I don't know where they
como es de derecha no sé dónde han
got that The truth is I don't know if Man Tenorio
sacado eso La verdad no sé si man tenor
has ever spoken out politically
se ha pronunciado políticamente en
but as he is
alguna ocasión pero que como es de
right-wing It's supposed to Well that it
derecha Se supone Pues que bueno que
was good that they occupied him I know
estaba bien que lo ocuparan yo que sé
something like that he said I don't remember what it was that they
algo así decía no me acuerdo cómo era lo
came to say but something like that okay it's like
que venían a decir pero algo así vale
okay
que es como a vale
Perfect perfect
Perfecto perfecto
Oh we have problems Well we're going to
Ay tenemos problemas Bueno lo vamos a
solve it we'll get ahead
solucionar saldremos adelante
if Haid
si haid
and David you
y David tú
say what  what's happening Aida please
dirás qué está pasando Aida por favor
noida my life no no no let's
noida mi vida
see I want to talk
ya no no a ver Quiero hablar
to Ay we have problems Well we're going to
con Ay tenemos problemas Bueno lo vamos
solve it we'll get ahead like
a solucionar saldremos adelante como
always Roco has already gone
siempre roco ya ha ido
and David you say come
y David tú dirás
back what's going on Aida please
vuelve qué está pasando Aida por favor
no no no no Aida my life
no no no no Aida mi vida
Okay San Lucas de Barrameda while they were going to
Ya San Lucas de barrameda mientras iban
talk to the squatters Of course they are
a hablar con los ocupas Claro que son
the squatters the squatters are upset
los ocupas los ocupas están molestos
because they don't want to be
porque no quieren que les
recorded they reconnect and
graben vuelven a conectar y aparece ahí
Nissar appears running after the alleged
nissar corriendo tras los presuntos
squatters with Patiño freaking out asking her to
ocupas con Patiño desquiciada pidiéndole
stop while no one is listening And they
que pare mientras nadie la escucha Y
almost come to blows again
casi vuelven a llegar a las manos
try to connect
intentar conectar
with one moment one moment
con un momento un momento
[Music]
[Música]
Where are you
A dónde
going no aa aa Stay there I beg you
vas no aa aa Quédate ahí te lo pido por
please it's an order
favor es una orden
an order do
una
n't you Hey, he doesn't
orden no te
hear you It's not that no it's not that no it's not that no it's not that no
Oye no te escucha No es que no es que no
This is not the
es que no es que no Esto no es la
purpose
finalidad
ID Hey the camera is listening to me
ID Oye me escucha el cámara me escucha
someone is listening to me but I don't know to what extent they
alguien pero yo no sé hasta qué punto
can record the squatters Listen to what I'm
pueden grabar a los ocupa Fíjate lo que
telling you eh
te digo eh
Listen to what I'm telling you that I think you can't
Fíjate lo que te digo que yo creo que no
record the squatters like that
puedes grabar así a los ocupa
eh You can't put it out in a medium eh It
eh No puedes sacarlo en un medio eh No
wasn't the squatters man I understand that it will
eran los ocupa hombre entiendo que sí
be when they are chasing them but I
será cuando los están persiguiendo pero
think that you can't record them really
es que creo que no los puedes grabar en
eh Let's see, I don't know to what extent you
eh A ver no sé hasta qué punto los
can put them in a
puedes poner en un
medium left off page it is supposed to be the
medio dejado de pag se supone que es el
marriage, don't
matrimonio no
see, no longer cut the image no no no
ve ya no cortar la imagen no no
how no
no cómo no
but the president of the community Javi they
peroo la presidenta de la comunidad Javi
are not the squatters No of course the squatter was the one
no son los ocupa No claro la ocupa era
who was in the va no to the squatters you can't
la que estaba en el va no a los ocupa no
record the owners Yes of
lo puedes grabar a los propietarios Sí
course you can't record them because
claro es que no los puedes grabar porque
they are anonymous people I don't know
son gente anónima no s
what confrontation between Yar for the lack of
qué enfrentamiento entre yar por la poca
empathy with his partner Let's
empatía con su compañera A
see Look I need one that you speak to me
ver Mira Necesito uno que me hables con
calmly because if not the communication is cut off
calma porque si no se se corta la
very calmly alter
comunicación con muchísima calma alterar
you pu you should have a little
ti pu deberías de tener un poco de
empathy with a person who has been
empatía con una persona que ha sido
received here at 10 in the morning with
recibida aquí a las 10 de la mañana con
swords raised okay dear
las espadas en alto de acuerdo querida
from the sofa it's very easy We have
desde el sofá es mu fácil Nosotros hemos
gone with all the tranquility to a
ido con toda la tranquilidad a un
restaurant from the sofa it is very it is very
restaurante desde el sofá es muy es muy
easy to give an opinion he says to the presenter I think
fácil opinar le dice a la presentadora
you are wrong I think you are
creo que te equivocas creo que te
wrong I think that  you are wrong at
equivocas creo que te equivocas en
any time In no way do we have
ningún momento En ningún tenemos
technical limitations I don't know what's
limitaciones técnicas desconozco lo que
going on I know what it's like to be a
está pasando conozco lo que es ser
reporter for many years Listen to
reportera durante muchísimos años
me for a moment Basque one are you going to
vascar uno me vas a escuchar un momento
listen to me for a moment dear are you going to listen to me at no
querida me vas a escuchar en ningún
time have I tried I tried to
momento he intentado he intentado
look down on your work I have
despreciar tu trabajo he intentado
simply tried to not let
simplemente que no se vaya de las manos
a situation that could harm
una situación que te puede perjudicar a
you and the program get out of hand I have tried to do it
ti y al programa lo he intentado hacer
in good faith that's what I have
de buena fe eso es lo que he
tried there is an account that neighbors have
intentado hay cuenta que vecinos han
attacked reporters from different
agredido a los reporteros de distintos
media outlets
medios
soaking us
empapándonos
I that the issue of squatters I don't fully
yo que el tema de los ocupas no termino
understand it here in Spain and I don't know
de de entenderlo aquí en España y no sé
why that happens The truth I mean I don't I don't fully
el Por qué pasa eso La verdad O sea yo
understand it or
es que no no lo termino de entender o
rather a property comes the owner
sea una propiedad viene el propietario
calls the police and they have to kick out the
llama la policía y tiene que echa la
people who are inside your property it's that they
gente que estén dentro de tu propiedad
shouldn't have It's that no I don't understand the
es que no debería tener Es que no no
mess I don't understand the mess the
entiendo el lío No entiendo el lío la
truth the mess No, the whole mess of the
verdad el lío No ya todo el lío de los
squatters I don't know
ocupa Yo es que no
the president of the community ended up
lo la presidenta de la comunidad terminó
with anxiety in the hospital it's that of course it's that you ca
con ansiedad en el hospital es que claro
n't bother a
es que ahí no puedes molestar a una
person who is the  president of the
persona que es la presidenta de la
community of a disabled person in the middle
comunidad de un discapacitado en medio
of a program I do
de un programa Yo es que lo de llamar a
n't understand when they came up with a
danisa no entiendo cuando les aparecido
good idea that it was to cancel the
buena idea que era para levantar el
program or whatever because
programa o lo que sea porque muchas
thank you very much anonymous Thank you very much
gracias anónimo Muchísimas gracias
by the way today they made me
son que por cierto hoy me hicieron
Manuel made me another visa I just
Manuel me hizo otro visum lo acabo de
saw it today at noon and I just saw it
ver hoy al mediodía y lo acabo de ver
now because he did it at 1 in the
ahora porque me lo ha hecho a la 1 de la
afternoon I don't know why or rather I don't
tarde no sé por qué o sea es que yo no
know this was a mistake on the part of
sé esto ha sido un error por parte de
the TV factory I mean I don't know
los de la fábrica de la tele o sea no sé
if they thought It's good that even though she's
si han pensado Que bueno que aunque sea
a conflictive person
una persona conflictiva
eh she can bring in an audience because of how
eh puede traer audiencia por lo
conflictive she is but she doesn't cross
conflictiva que es pero no traspasa la
the line for me Aida crosses
traspasa la línea para mí Aida traspasa
the line of what is morbid and let's go
la línea de lo que es el morbo y vamos a
see it because of Lía and such no no she
verlo por la que Lía y tal a que no a
messes it up all the programs that are here
caga todos los programas que están aquí
since 10 in the morning and others that
desde las 10 de la mañana y otros que
have even lasted all night here with their
han hecho incluso noche aquí con las
swords raised they have sprayed us with bleach they
espadas en alto nos han rociado de lejía
have sprayed us with hoses they have
nos han rociado con mangueras nos han
spat on us  they have
escupido nos han
insulted me and I have limited myself to going to the
insultado y me he limitado a ir al
restaurant where they have treated us so extremely
restaurante que nos han tratado tan suma
extremely you take a car and it is a
tan sumamente tú coges un coche y es un
robbery instead they break into your house and they
robo en cambio te entran en la casa y se
stay and no but it is that on top of that apparently let's
quedan y no pero es que encima por lo
see I do not understand very well how I
visto a ver yo no entiendo muy bien como
read it but I think that you can not even
La leí pero creo que no le puedes ni
cut off the light or the water on top of that I
cortar la luz ni el agua encima yo que
know a move that you say come on I am
sé una movida que tú dices vamos yo
freaking out or rather I do not understand the thing about the squatters here in
flipo o sea yo lo de los ocupa aquí en
Spain eh I do not know if in
España no lo entiendo eh No sé si en
other countries they will have the same problem
otros países tendrán el mismo problema
the same way of
la misma forma de
handling it but I do not no I do not understand I mean even if
llevarlo pero yo no no no entiendo O sea
I have five properties okay
aunque yo tenga cinco propiedades vale
I have bought five properties they
yo me he comprado cinco propiedades
break into one of them and I want to
entran en una de ellas y quiero
throw them out you call the police the police
echarlos llamas a la policía la policía
go and they have to remove it is that no I do not
va y los Tiene que sacar es que no no le
see it but instantly I mean I do not
veo pero al instante o sea es que no le
see the complication that they have put into
veo la complicación que le han puesto a
that and that is what they have done you know with the
eso y es lo que han hecho sabes con la
law I do not understand I do not understand she comes this
ley no entiendo no entiendo viene esta
afternoon and I found the president
tarde y me he encontrado a la presidenta
having a shot So it was my
tomando un chupito Entonces ha sido mi
surprise the one who had pretended that she wanted
sorpresa la que había fingido que quería
an age attack found me there
un ataque deedad me ha encontrado allí
a little bit Okay but it's that  it doesn't
un poquito Bueno pero es que da igual o
matter, I mean, the president doesn't have to. I
sea la presidenta no te tiene por qué O
mean, maybe she told you whatever to get them to
sea a lo mejor te ha dicho lo que sea
leave her, I just don't
para que la dejen es que no lo
understand. I don't understand,
entiendo es que no no lo entiendo la
honestly, I don't understand the part about bothering the president. Let's
verdad lo de molestar a la presidenta no
see what the hell
lo he entendido a ver qué [__] tiene que
a woman who blames
ver una mujer que culpa de lo que le
Manu Tenorio for what happens in his apartment has to do with it. I mean, if
pase a Manu Tenorio en su piso o sea si
the president of the community
la presidenta de la comunidad lo que
basically does... Well, look,
hace es básicamente Pues mira pues
man, Alicia, tell us how you
hombre Alicia cuenta qué tal
are, the expense of lawsuits and paperwork is horrible
estás es horrible el gasto de juicios y
and it takes a long time,
papeles y va para largo
but the president of the community does
pero la presidenta de la comunidad lo
is collect the community fees and little
que hace es cobrar la comunidad y poco
else, and manage when there's
más no y gestionar cuando hay alguna
something she has to do. Don't pay attention. Ah,
cosa que tenga que hacer No atend Ah
daniza. And then when we
daniza Y entonces cuando la hemos
caught her with the camera before going
pillado con la cámara antes de entrar en
live, she became extremely
el directo se ha puesto como una
angry. I just wanted to hear the
energumen yo solo quería escuchar el
president's testimony to find out
testimonio de la presidenta para saber
why they are supporting the tenants in such a way. She
por están apoyando de manera tan a los
is supporting the
está apoyando los
squatting tenants, that Matamoros, I have to
inquilinos ocupas que Matamoros te tengo
correct you. It's a term called
que corregir Es un término se llama in
inocupas. The tenant who with a legitimate
ocupas el inquilino que con un legítimo
contract stops paying becomes an
contrato deja de pagar se convierte en
squatter. Ah, so it's not an squatter.  has gotten
ocupa ya Ah o sea que no es un ocupa que
involved I mean, it
se le haya metido
's not a
sea no es un
squatter, it's not a squatter that they are not
ocupa no es un ocupa que se no son unos
squatters that have gotten involved but rather
ocupa que se le hayan metido sino que
tenants that have stopped
son unos inquilinos que han dejado de
paying of course so I can imagine
pagar claro entonces me imagino por
where the story is going to go I'm going to
dónde va ir la historia voy a seguir
keep watching but maybe I'm right I think they're going to be a family I think they're going to be a family that the whole building knows and cares about because they've been there for a long time and for whatever reason things have gone wrong for them in life and they can't
en la vida y no pueden
pay and that's the explanation why
pagar y por eso es la explicación de que
the neighbors are supporting them and something like that
le estén apoyando los vecinos y algo
so you see how you have to listen to
entonces veis comoo hay que escuchar las
things man you
cosas tío
always have to listen to
siempre hay que hay que escuchar las
things eh you
cosas eh
always have to listen to things and the
hay que escuchar las cosas siempre y las
versions that you obviously don't justify
versiones que no justifica evidentemente
Lili very good no
Lili buenísimo no
María Patiño In company no Knowing
María Patiño En compañía no Sabiendo
how to manage that there is Danisa
Cómo gestionar que hay danisa esté
buying tickets for this to end
comprando papeleta para que esto acabe
badly in an atmosphere that is already quite
mal en un ambiente que ya está bastante
heated in
caldeado de por
itself is that it is a very bad idea eh what Aida did was a very
sí es que es malísima idea eh lo de Aida
bad idea wait a moment Aida I have
ha sido malísima idea un momento aa Aida
heard your story and I
he escuchado tu relato y condeno
publicly condemn the treatment you have received and
públicamente el trato que has recibido y
that would never  applaud they do it
eso jamás lo aplaudir se lo hagan
even to my greatest enemy what I have
incluso a mi mayor enemigo lo que yo he
tried is that this person to whom
intentado es que esta persona a la que
you have gone to to obtain information
tú has acudido para obtener información
and do his
y hacer su
job Javi according to what
trabajo Javi según dijo el abogado de
Mano Tenorio's lawyer said said that they both work
mano Tenorio dijo que los dos trabajan
That's what he said eh Of course but here everyone
Eso dijo eh Claro pero aquí cada uno
has their version because I imagine
tiene su versión porque yo me imagino
that of course from Manu Tenorio's perspective he
que claro desde la perspectiva de Manu
is seeing that they are two
Tenorio pues está viendo que son dos
people who have their jobs and that they
personas que tienen su trabajo y que le
have stopped paying him I don't know how
han dejado a él de pagar yo no sé cómo
Manu Tenorio's things are going but maybe it
le irá Manu Tenorio las cosas pero a lo
is an income that he needs every month
mejor es un ingreso que necesita al mes
or or that or that he counts on that income every
o o que o que cuenta con ese ingreso al
month
mes
for him you understand In fact yes let's go I do
para él me entienden De hecho sí vamos
n't know Okay well of course maybe
No lo sé Vale pues claro a lo mejor
from the tenants' perspective
desde la perspectiva de los inquilino
something has happened to them and I
pues les ha venido algo al revés y
understand that let's see is that of course what we
entiendo que a ver es que claro lo que
would have to see is that if they have paid all their
habría que ver es que si han pagado toda
lives and suddenly they stop paying damn it is
la vida y de repente dejan de pagar [__]
assumed that something must have happened it
pues se supone que algo habrá pasado no
is not to justify it or or to say that it
es por justificarlo ni ni ni decir que
is fine but let's go
está bien pero vamos
given the way he has reacted I have
ante la manera que ha reaccionado he
tried to prevent this from going any further for
intentado que esto no llegase a más por
you and for us that is the only thing I have
ti y por nosotros es lo único que he
tried but  Of course I support you on
intentado pero desde luego te apoyo
this pl and I fully understand that it must have
este pl y entiendo perfectamente que has
been a very
tenido que ser una situación muy
uncomfortable situation for
incómoda para
you right now my
ti por ahora mis
teng sieren Roar of no because everyone is
teng sieren Roar de no porque está todo
with their swords raised
el mundo con las espadas en alto
protecting what could happen tomorrow to
protegiendo lo que mañana puede sucer a
each
cada
spectator because the president doesn't want to talk
espectador por no quiere hablar la
the president doesn't want to talk because she
la presidenta no quiere hablar porque
simply supports these
Sencillamente apoya a estos inquilinos
squatters who according to her feel very sorry for them
ocupas que según ella le dan mucha pena
because Manu Tenorio has a lot of money
porque Manu Tenorio tiene mucho dinerito
like he told me and they don't
como a ti me ha dicho y y ellos no
have anything which is not true because they have
tienen nada cosa que no es cierta porque
promised a house and they are
han dejado apalabrado una casa y están
paying a mortgage really is that
pagando una hipoteca realmente es que
the reality if that is the
esa es la realidad si ese es el
argument it is an argument that
argumento es un argumento que a mí
personally does not work for me the fact that
particularmente no me vale el hecho de
you have economic power does
que tú tengas un poder económico
not stop you from becoming a victim of
no deja de convertirte en víctima de una
justice come on let's see the
justicia vamos vamos a ver la
arrival companion excuse me if I con
llegada compañera discúlpame si me con
car please but my camera which couldn't
car favor pero mi cámara que no puede
be more brilliant Juan is the poor thing
ser más brillante Juan está el pobre
terrified because they have thrown his
atemorizado porque le han tirado el
mobile phone at him they have attacked him they have spat on him and we
móvil le han agredido le han escupido y
are waiting for them to arrive here with
estamos esperando a que lleguen aquí con
sticks is that the next one going to do that
palos es que los siguiente va a hacer
Well I have
eso Bueno yo tengo
faith I have faith  in which people who do not
fe Tengo fe en que personas que no estén
agree with the situation that has been
de acuerdo con la situación que se ha
made public Paquita Paquita darling I
hecho pública Paquita Paquita cariño Yo
know that you do it without bad intentions but
sé que lo hacéis sin mala intención pero
not promotion small channels is what you
no promocion canales pequeños es que me
are telling me is appearing on the Channel
estás diciendo está saliendo en el Canal
of I don't know who I appear on all those
de no sé quién yo salgo en todos esos
channels every day those channels
canales todos los días esos canales
are only about me, about me or
tratan Solamente sobre mí sobre mí o
about dala they only live off us
sobre dala únicamente viven de nosotros
parasitizing So no promotion because
parasitando Entonces no promocion porque
the moderators are going to ban you I
os van a banear los moderadores os lo
tell you more than anything so that they do not ban you
digo más que nada para que noos baneen
okay that every day that's not for me Let me
vale eso todos los días eso no a mí me
know when it comes out on Tele5 Javi that they
Avísame cuando salga en tele5 Javi que
are putting a video of yours on Tele5
están poniendo un vídeo tuyo en tele5
but that it comes out on a parasitic channel that is
pero que salga en un canal parásito que
about me that is not a
trata sobre mí eso no es ninguna
surprise darling evidently they are not going to be
sorpresa cariño evidentemente no van a
contained on their own that they
ser contenido por su cuenta que le
occupy the house in Fuerteventura
ocupen la casa de fuerteventura la
Patiño who is very understanding
Patiño que es muy comprensiva
exactly let's see clearly Here we have to
exactamente a ver claro Es que aquí hay
listen to all versions because
que escuchar todas las versiones porque
now look what Aida says that they are
ahora fíjate lo que dice Aida que están
paying a mortgage That I don't know
pagando una hipoteca Que no sé
what to do otherwise I have faith
qué actuar de otra manera Tengo fe
because we all have the capacity to
porque todos tenemos capacidad de
argue that
argumentar
here comes someone seems good to me let's see I did
esa aquí viene algui me parece bien a
not see p  or they come with
ver no vi de p o vienen con
Calm down, calm down,
Tranquila tranquila
true, but I
verad pero
saw
vi salg
exit, it seems
sal parece
great,
estupendo
call, exhausted to the door
llama reventado hasta la puerta
Mara, you live here,
Mara ustedes viven aquí
delighted, delighted, but you are what you
encantada encantada pero ustedes son lo
occupy, it's not worth it, okay, and you pay
que ocupan no vale vale Y ustedes pagan
your
su
rent. Oh, and also, well, very
alquiler Ah que también pues ya muy
little, not for being a minor, I don't
poito no para ser menor de edad no te
see you, you're already in your twenties, you see Aida. Those
veo ya entrado en añ lo ves Aida Esas
are the things that you and I are not going to
son las cosas que tú y yo no nos vamos a
understand each other. Listen to me for a moment, honey,
entender Escúchame un momento cariño
listen to me, I swear I'm not against
escúchame que te juro que no voy contra
you. Listen to me for a second, eh, let's
ti Escúchame un segundo eh vamos a
try, since tempers are
intentar ya que están los ánimos
high, not to hurt feelings, yes, I
calientes no herir sensibilidades si
tried to handle,
intent manejar
you president,
yolar presidenta
coming, it seems fine to me. Maybe I saw.
viniendo me parece bien A lo mejor vi
Talk to
Hablar a
dialogue, Sia,
dialogar Sia
but don't scare me,
pero no me asustes
aa Aida. Don't scare me, it's very, well,
aa Aida No me asustes es muy pues
then because there are images that
entonces car que hay imágenes que no
the program cannot broadcast, well,
puede emitir el programa pues entonces
I'm not the director there, please,
yo no soy la directora ahí por favor
mate, what do you
compañer qui
mean, the
decir la
police came in, don't come in there, it's
poliía entr es no entres ahí es
private property. First, Norma, what is
propiedad privada primera Norma cuál es
your, what do you want to do? It
tu qué es lo que quieres hacer dich
's a
es una zona
public area with a fence, no, Aida. What's the
pública con una verja no Aida Cuál es el
next step? What do you want? Where do you
siguiente paso Qué quieres A dónde
want?  No, I don't want to, Maria,
quieres llegar No yo no quiero María a
I would love to talk to those who
mí me encantaría hablar con los que
occupy it and know their version as they want to
ocupa y saber su versión como la quieren
know it, of course, there were only a few of us and the
saber claro éramos pocos y acude la
police come. Look, this is going to bring
policía Mira esto le va a traer
problems. Eh, This is going to bring
problemas Eh Esto les va a traer
problems, eh, to the
problemas eh al
program, eh, we now have live images.
programa eh tenemos ahora imágenes en
The police have arrived right now,
directo ha llegado la policía en estos
direct, then,
momentos directo entonces
lose, can I tell them? I am the
perd puedo decírselo soy la
one in charge. Please, the National Police,
mandada por favor la Policía Nacional
who have protected us so much,
que tanto nos nos ha protegido
previously, that came and thanks to them, they
anteriormente que vino y gracias a ellos
removed the bleach, removed the hose
retiraron la lejía retiraron la manguera
and removed everything, is asking me to
y retiraron todo me está pidiendo que
please cut the broadcast for a moment,
por favor cortamos un momento la emisión
Mr. Director,
señor director
of course. Yes, yes, right now,
por supuesto Sí sí Ahora mismo se corta
the broadcast is going to be cut. Right now, talk to the
la emisión ahora mismo habla con la
police and we'll see what
policía y veremos a ver qué es lo que
happens. The president's daughter is calling. She's already calling as a
ocurre la hija de la presidenta llama ya
mediator. Just a moment, you'll see how Maria
mediadora un momento verás tú como María
Patiño gets more information from her from the
Patiño le saca más información desde el
set than the one who's causing trouble there. Just a
plató que la ida la que está liando ahí
moment, you'll see how Maria
un momento tú verá tú como a la María
Patiño gets more information from her in another way
Patiño con otra forma le saca más
than there is from there. I
información que la hay de ahí Es que yo
see it as a mistake, the truth is, I don't know at what
lo veo un error la verdad no sé en qué
point this seemed like a good idea. I
momento les ha parecido buena idea esto
mean, when are they supposed to be about inclusive people?
O sea cuando se supone que van de gente
Hey, they support the weakest people
Eh que que apoyan a las personas más
and all that, don't they suddenly put you in there,
débiles y demás no de repente te meten
Danisa? It's good that you act the way you act, no,
ahí danisa Que bueno actúa como actúa no
wait, it's
esa espera eres
you, it's you, it's you, Ana.
tú eres tú
Oh, Ana, Ana, wait, daughter, one
Ana Ay Ana Ana espérate hija que un
moment, tell me yes. Let's see, wait. Calm down,
momento dime si A ver espérate Tranquila
calm down, but listen to
tranquila pero escúchame escúchame
me, listen to me. Calm down, because I know the situation is complicated, the only thing I'm trying to do here is find out what's going on and and and relax, okay, let's see, I'm Maria Patiño, okay, people can listen to you, what you
vale puede escucharte la gente lo que
want to tell me, you're going to talk only
quieres decirme vas a hablar solo
to me,
conmigo
okay, okay, because the other thing, I'm not going to do that
valeo porque lo otro no voy a hac eso
because everything that's there, everything that's been
porque ya todo lo que está todo lo que
said, it's already been said on one channel, I know, on another, everything has already been
se ha dicho ya está eso ya en una cadena
said. Here, we don't
se en otra ya está ha dicho todo aquí no
want to cause a problem or anything. What
queremos metern un problema ni nada Lo
happens is that here, I understand that ID
que pasa que aquí yo entiendo que ha ID
does a very specific type of television
hace un tipo de televisión muy
to look for conflict, to look for
específica para buscar conflicto buscar
problems, but the thing is that since this morning
problema pero es que desde esta mañana
that I have tried to talk to her in a
que yo he intentado hablar con ella de
good way and I have everything recorded, telling her
buena y tengo todo grabado diciéndole
that she doesn't record me, that she doesn't record my
que ni me graba a mí que ni grabe mi
family or at home, and she's looking for
familia ni en casa y está buscando
problems, to the point that she has even come
problemas al punto que ha venido incluso
to the door of my house, recording.
hasta a la puerta de mi casa grab para
inside Me telling her that my mother was
dentro Yo diciéndole que mi madre se
feeling ill and she has continued continued
encontraba mal y ella ha seguido ha
and continued and has not been
seguido y ha seguido y no ha está
chasing me to go to H such and such too
persiguiendo para ir al H tal también ya
and I have all of this recorded I have
y todo esto lo tengo grabado lo tengo
warned you are the you are the daughter of
advertido tú eres la eres la hija de
the Let's see she is very nervous let's see do
la A ver es que está muy nerviosa a ver
you love Ana right yes And your mother is the
te amas Ana verdad sí Y tu madre es la
president right yes okay And then
presidenta verdad sí vale Y entonces
uh you have felt a little invaded
eh tú te has sentido un poco invadida
by for for well for the character
por por por bueno por por el carácter a
maybe of Aida that I will now speak
lo mejor de Aida que yo ahora hablaré
to her because I do not want her to be
con ella porque tampoco quiero que se
offended and Understand me because I am
ofenda y Entiéndeme a mí porque yo estoy
here trying to Listen listening to
aquí intentando Escuchar escuchando a
both of them The question is for me to
las dos La pregunta es para yo
understand it okay uh your mother as
entenderlo vale eh tu madre como
president supports Manu Tenorio or
presidenta apoya a a Manu Tenorio o a
those who are presumably there let's see look I am
los que presuntamente están ahí a ver
telling you uh here my mother as
mir te lo digo eh aquí mi madre como
president and like any other neighbor
presidenta y como cualquier otro vecino
who can tell you we are not leaving
que te puede decir nosotros no nos vamos
Well in favor of neither one nor the other but
Pos a favor ni de uno ni de otro sino
here they have come to ask
que aquí la se han venido a preguntar
how the coexistence is
que cóm es la conviv
and also I can tell you and it is a
y tamb te lo pued de y de es una
coexistence it is a family  that doesn't give
convivencia es una famil que no da
because true
porque verd
seeing clearly I understand you it's like let's
viendo claro yo te entiendo es como a
see There is a problem between Manu Tenorio and
ver Hay un problema entre Manu Tenorio y
some tenants they don't bother me
unos inquilinos a m no me dan la lata yo
because I have to take a position no Of course
por me tengo que posicionar no Claro
we simply came to ask
nosotros simplemente se Vení a preguntar
how is the coexistence we
que cóm es la convivencia nosotros
answered such a day and already H I know quar Cos
respondimos tal día y ya H se quar Cos
But he has demanded saying that as we have
Pero ha exigiendo diciendo que como
been Talking to other programs that you
hemos ido Hablar a otros programas que
also have to talk for noses
también tenéis que hablar por narices
here Well look, maybe they are
aquí Pues mira yo fíjate a lo mejor me
going to kick me out of my program but I am one
van a echar de mi programa pero yo soy
of those who defend the freedom of each
de las que defiendo la libertad de cada
one speak for whoever they want and where they
uno habla para quien quiere y donde
want then too It is true that
quiere entonces también Es verdad que a
maybe Aida she is a perfectionist
lo mejor Aida ella es muy perfeccionista
and wants to do her job well and in that
y quiere hacer bien su trabajo y en ese
sense in the intention of
sentido en la intención de la de la
perfection and of achieving everything sometimes
perfección y de conseguir todo a veces a
things get out of hand for me too
mí también se me van las cosas de la
I ask your forgiveness I am
mano yo te pido perdón
going to try
voy intentar
haot And to all this Man Tenor does not want to
haot Y a todo esto man tenor no quiere
know anything about them and
saber nada de ellos y les
blocks them which makes her end up
bloquea lo que hace que termine de
exploding and she leaves
estallar y se vaya
crying Manu Tenorio has given some kind
llorando Manu Tenorio ha dado algún tipo
of statement somewhere
de declaración en alguna parte
has led to a  Calvary situation
ha llevado a una situación de Calvario
for Mr. Manu Tenorio and Manu Tenorio
al Señor Manu Tenorio y Manu Tenorio en
instead of showing his face and telling the whole
vez de dar la cara y decir toda la
truth Now he also hides and
verdad Ahora también se esconde y nos
hangs up on us Well, let them
cuelga el teléfono Pues nada que le
have his house occupied for the rest of his
tengan la casa ocupada el resto de la
life Jai what's happening tomorrow double session no
vida Jai qué pasa mañana sesión doble no
pod
pod
okay I was talking to the
vale que estaba hablando con el
coach that's it because here one is
entrenador ya está porque aquí una se
breaking her face helping Manu Tenorio
parte la cara por ayudar a Manu Tenorio
for wanting to listen to the five squatters And on
por querer Escuchar a Los cinco ocupas Y
top of that they're going to break me now
encima me la van a partir a mí ahora
man No man no Well it seems
hombre No hombre no Bueno me parece
reasonable to me
razonable
with
con
education let's see I want to send a
educación a ver yo quiero mandar un
message of
mensaje de
encouragement
ánimo
bu collapsed I think that the one who should
bu derrumbada yo creo que a quien habría
send a message of encouragement is to the
que mandar un mensaje de ánimo es a los
entire community
tod la comunidad
mother of God Hey we still have to see
madre de Dios Oye que nos falta por ver
that I can't
que no me lo Puedo
skip it no lack of seeing that
saltar no falta por ver que
yuji what happens is that I don't know who sent it to
yuji lo que pasa que es que no sé quién
me Where is Yuji's who sent it to me
quién me la ha mandado no me la ha
Pili didn't send it to me I thought Pili sent it
Pili yo creía que la haba mandado la
Yuji's And who sent it to me
yuji Y quién me la ha mandado
then who sent me Yui
entonces quién me ha mandado de yui
then
entonces
Oh it was  luare
Ah sido luare
luare yuji posted this but I don't know what it
luare yuji ha puesto esto pero no sé qué
means what do you think this means
significa qué creéis que significa esto
how is he
cómo lo
all day with such a
está todo el día con con
pullita why are they so calm
pullita que por qué están tan tranquilos
Why are they so calm
Por qué están tan tranquilos
Haha I'm above
Jaja Estoy por encima de
you but it's very far-fetched
ti pero es muy rebuscado
no no no no I don't need to use the translator
no no no no necesito usar el traductor
I know what it says Why is it so so
Yo sé lo que pone Por qué es tan tan
chill Hahaha
chill Jajaja
but maybe it has nothing to do with it
pero a lo mejor no tiene nada que ver
no I mean maybe no no no
no O sea a lo mejor no no es ninguna
no mm
no mm
self-criticism How's the
autocrítica Cómo va el vídeo del
main video going mm a
principal mm ha saltado un
cop jumped out a copy jumped out
copin ha salta un copy
Hey the video is going well
Oye por el vídeo va bien
eh No but maybe it's a video that he
eh No pero a lo mejor es un vídeo que ha
simply shared and that's it
compartido simplemente y ya está
No maybe just a video that I
No a lo mejor simplemente un vídeo que
shared of animals and outside no or what
comp de animales y fuera no o qué
and then we have this one that's
y luego tenemos esta que me está
sending me places now but it's that she translated it for me
mandando lugares ahora pero es que me lo
places Look pin when you
ha traducido lugares Mira pin cuando
force a woman to go through everything
obligas a una mujer para pasar por todo
she's afraid you create a woman who
ella tiene miedo tú creas una mujer que
has nothing to fear anymore
no tiene nada para temer más
When you make a
Cuando haces que una
woman when you force a woman to
mujer cuando obligas a una mujer a
go through everything or rather like she's
pasar por todo o sea en plan que tiene
very afraid of something that scares her a lot
mucho miedo por algo que le da mucho
then the  you get stronger no and she's
miedo pues la haces más fuerte no y ya
not afraid of
no tiene miedo a
anything anymore I'm just like these things dude What does
nada Yo es que estas cosas tío Qué dice
alanne say Not necessarily everything she
alanne No necesariamente todo lo que
posts has to do with the
ponga tiene que tiene que ver con el
subject but with this lady know man I
tema pero con esta señora saber hombre
think this one does And this one no I think
Yo creo que este sí Y este no yo creo
this one doesn't and I think this is a
que este no y yo creo que esto es un
video that she shared that is not
vídeo que ha compartido que además no es
even from her unless the song says
ni de ella a no ser que la canción diga
something else because this is a video Look 58 it
algo más porque esto es un vídeo Mira 58
says here in this capture you see it
pone aquí en esta captura lo ves
then I don't know if the song says
entonces a no sé que la canción diga
something in the lyrics
algo en la letra
you know but I think this does Eh This
saes pero yo creo que esto sí Eh Esto sí
is like you've already made me go through something
es como ya me has hecho pasar por algo
no I'm not afraid of anything anymore but let's see
no ya no tengo miedo de nada pero a ver
if FR has
si FR la ha
blocked her Fran has blocked her from
bloqueado Fran la ha bloqueado de todas
everywhere doesn't want to know anything about her anymore
partes no quiere saber más nada de ella
and
y
basically today Fran was already making
básicamente hoy Estaba Fran ya haciendo
her animal videos and a live
sus vídeos de animales y un directo
show I don't know what things about
enseñando no sé qué cosas de los
animals that he was showing
animales de estaba enseñando estaba
Fran was doing a live show today for
haciendo Fran un directo hoy para
members about animals So what she
miembros sobre los animales Entonces ya
has to do No Look for anything else
lo que tiene que hacer No Busca más nada
no
no
anyway Alan how I
en fin Alan como la hab
passed by I'm going to see what
pasado a ver voy a ver qué es lo que me
Pili de
Pili de
moñ sent me that she sent me wait I'm not going  make you
moñ que me ha mandado espérate no voy
filter something strange here I'm
hac que filtros por aquí algo raro
going to see what Pili de moño sends me because it
voy a ver que me manda Pili de
seems that
moño que por lo visto que me han
some ladies have defended me it's true also
defendido unas señoras es verdad además
the image has the phoenix it's true it
la imagen tiene el ave Fénix es verdad
's true I had seen it man I hadn't thought
es verdad lo había visto tío no había
to comment it's true you're
caído en comentarlo es verdad tienes
right luar let's see apparently there are a
razón luar a ver por lo visto hay unas
few ladies I don't know if they are from the
cuantas señoras no sé si son las del
patri
patri
space well but but it's that they laugh at
espacio pues pero pero es que se ríen de
us that's what they think
nosotros eso es que se piensa se piensa
people think that we are idiots they see our
la gente que somos imbéciles nos ven la
stupid faces and where they say I say no the
cara de tontos y donde dicen digo no la
face we can't see it because
cara no lo podemos ver porque tenéis la
most of you have a little dog this this that
mayoría un perrito un este lo otro a mí
yes she can see my face now eh look at my
sí me puede ver la cara ahora eh mirarme
face Diego I understand seeing
la cara Diego entiendo viendo la actitud
Peppa's attitude that she didn't like
de Peppa que no le habrá gustado mucho
the space very much no So they have
el espacio no O sea que nos han
defended those that she hates No I
defendido a los que a ella odia No yo
said no no first they said that she had I don't
dije no no primero decían que tenía no
know how many operations that she had
sé cuántas operaciones que le hab
first they said that she had I don't know how many
primero decían que tenía no sé cuántas
operations have you heard on some
operaciones habéis escuchado en algún
channel this afternoon there is a certain Lola from e
canal esta tarde está una tal Lola de e
con host around here it has never been said
con anfitrión por aquí nunca se ha dicho
that but well if you  you want to lie okay
eso pero bueno si ustedes queréis mentir
things that had metastases they
vale noas cosas que tenía metástasis
say no that it was misunderstood no that it is
dicen que no que se entendió mal no que
wrong seg says patriotic yil they are In my
mal seg dice patrio yil son En mi
opinion totally totally J fans You'll
opinión fanáticas de J totalmente
see
totalmente Ya lo veréis
now seens that people It's imbecile and stupid
ahora seens que gente Es imbécil y tonta
what they think but of that it is I mean that
lo que se piensan pero de de que sea O
they think about what it is no no no no no no
sea que piensen a lo que es no no no no
yeah when we finish this I'm going to
no no ya ya cuando terminemos esto voy a
put up a survey to see what
poner una encuesta a ver qué piensa la
people think if you are imbeciles or stupid or or
gente si sois imbéciles o tontas o o
complete and utter fools this
tontas del
is insulted because you're
culo está insulta porque estás
insulting the women in space like that stupid
insultando así a las del espacio tontas
idiots complete and utter fools
imbéciles tontas del
because time with this issue that it's been a while since
culo porque tiempo con el tema ese que
the flight said that it was a
ya hace tiempo que el vuelo dijo que era
lie that he had nothing the flight God you
mentira que no tenía nada el vuelo Dios
have put girl what an example you have put
has puesto tía qué ejempl has puesto
my mother it came from the soul eh that the
madre mía ha salido del alma eh que el
smell said and what's going on cl the flight is
huelo dijo y qué pasa cl el vuelo es
Central Hospital of course man I don't think they are
Central claro hombre Yo no creo que sean
Santos but they have brought out a lot of
Santos pero han sacado un montón de
information on this issue that the truth has been
informaciones de este tema que la verdad
noo yes a Peta for each
noo si una Peta cada
Spaniard but not to m a d they have to Javi
español pero no a m a d tienen que Javi
really confess already  that you killed
de verdad confiesa ya que has matado a
Manolete kiss s
manolete beso s
Hera that some audio
hera que se habían visto unos audios
recordings had been seen that the sister said it was a
oídos de que la hermana decía que era
lie that well This comes from this
mentira que bueno Esto viene de de esto
comes from what the flight says because no no they have not
viene de lo que dice el vuelo porque no
shown any proof what
no no ha mostrado ninguna prueba lo que
the flight says what Cris says what
dice el vuelo lo que dice n Cris lo que
Marca Gui says but here nobody shows
dice marca gui pero aquí nadie muestra
anything eh No no no here everything is from Boquilla
nada eh No no no aquí todo de Boquilla
here everything is from Boquilla but I don't
aquí todo de Boquilla pero es que no
understand this I really don't
entiendo lo de esto yo de verdad no lo
understand But what is it that is from
entiendo Pero qué es lo que es de
Boquilla hasn't Lolly herself said that she
Boquilla no ha dicho la propia
hasn't had cancer that she
Lolly que no ha tenido cáncer que se lo
made it up is that what is that I do
inventó
n't
es que lo de es que no lo
understand is that we were talking about it
entiendo es que lo estuvimos hablando
yesterday well It's that I wouldn't even bring up this topic
ayer buen Es que yo ya este tema yo ni
anymore if it were her she didn't say that she was
lo sacaba más si fuera ella no dijo que
going to ban she didn't say that she was going to ban the
iba a banear no dijo que iba a banear el
topic so that they wouldn't mention it what
tema para que no lo mencionaran lo que
happens is that she gets angry because she thinks she's going to
pasa es que se pica porque se cree que
deceive People you know not like you who
va a engañar La gente sabes no como tú
show everything Exactly
que lo muestras todo Exactamente
self-criticism no no but you know what
autocrítica no no pero sabes qué es lo
happens that she gets angry she thinks that
que pasa que se pica se cree que la
people are going to fall for her lies and  she's going to
gente va a caer en sus mentiras y se va
forget the next day no ma'am hers hers
a olvidar el día siguiente no señora lo
already
suyo ya
people are not going to forget
lo suyo la gente no lo va a olvidar
Peppa yours people and look at
Peppa lo tuyo la gente y mira que
some collaborators of the patri of the
algunas colaboradoras del patri del
space of the patri patri space
espacio de la patri patri espacio
some of them don't like me eh but let's
algunas no les caigo yo bien eh pero a
see It's that this is unanimous this
ver Es que esto es unánime esto ya solo
is only from people like you Peppa that
es de de gente como tú Peppa que que
the lie will continue simply out of
vaya a seguir la mentira simplemente por
hate not out of
odio no por
logic here everything is from Boquilla de Boquilla
lógica aquí todo de Boquilla de Boquilla
It's that from Boquilla that more than proving
Es que de Boquilla que más que demostrar
that
que se lo inventó
Ana Sánchez made it up Well I'm about to make a
Ana Sánchez Pues yo estoy por hacer un
video of this woman on the
vídeo de esta mujer en el canal
main channel like a video that's not going to
principal en plan vídeo que no le va a
give her any fame because she's not going to earn
dar nada de fama porque no va a ganar
anything you know but well with all my clips
nada sabes pero bien con todos mis clips
of these good videos that I make
de estos vídeos buenos que yo hago en
like with all the clips from the
plan con todos los clips desde el
beginning Pin Pin Pin you know pin pan What does the
principio Pin Pin Pin sabes pin pan Qué
Indian say what happens is that he saw
dice indio lo que pasa es que ha visto
that Loli has liquidity again that's why he
que Loli vuelve a tener liquidez por eso
did this to defend her but of course
ha hecho esto para defenderla pero claro
but the ard of
pero es que el ard de
Troy the one of Troy already gives
Troya el de Troya ya se des
and came out in an audio saying that he had
y salió en un audio diciendo que había
followed Loli's Lie to cover her
seguido La Mentira de Loli para cubrirla
So there is no more debate
Entonces ya no hay ya no hay más debate
Because  They come out now again saying
Porque salen ahora otra vez diciendo que
no if they themselves said that you know that
no si ya ellos mismos dijeron que sabes
Loli's purse doesn't make sense but I paid
sentido el monedero de la Loli per hecho
a lot of attention because the subject is true
mucho caso porque el tema es verdad lo
I had it all you habab hab habl peris no
tení tod you habab hab habl peris no
Here no
Aquí
here no
no aquí no
here it has been talked about when Mrs.
aquí se ha hablado cuando la señora
Lolta has wanted to talk about her own
lolta ha querido hablar de su propia
illness Here no here we have always refused to
enfermedad Aquí no aquí nos hemos negado
do it Sorry I've even gotten an
hacerlo Perdón que me ha entrado hasta
allergy because I'm allergic to lies
alergia que soy alérgico a las mentiras
that there not In your channel
que ahí no En su canal no se ha hablado
Loli's illness has not been talked about here you are saying
de la enfermedad de Loli está diciendo
that the illness has not been talked about here
que aquí no se ha hablado de la
But if it is born here yes it
enfermedad Pero si aquí nace si de aquí
comes out from here and I am not ashamed at all So
sale y yo no le da vergüenza ninguna Así
if you put me in the same bag that now you're
que si me metes en el saco que ahora me
going to put me in another bag
vas a meter cer otro saco
eh no that I never pay attention to it
eh que no que nunca le presto atención
but now I see that they are already
pero es que ahora veo que ya están
recognizing that it has not had to
reconociendo que que no ha tenido que
do any and that no that we understood it
hacer ninguno y que no que lo entendimos
wrong or that they thought wrong and that no that it
mal o que se pensaron mal y que que no
was not what we thought that she used
que no era lo que pensamos que utilizó
the wrong words Then if when you finish
mal las palabras Luego si cuando acabéis
if you want I will op about it but
si queréis yo me op al respecto pero
But Javi this woman who is She is one that well she
Pero Javi esta mujer quién es Es una que
was one  Big Brother contestant, one
bueno era una concursante gran hermano
of those that happen and you don't even remember
de estas que pasan y ni te acuerdas de
who she is, one of those that happen anonymously,
quién es de estas que pasan anónimamente
but for balls she wants to be in all
pero por huevos quiere estar en todos
the [ __ ] you know And then when she saw
los sarados sabes Y entonces cuando vio
here that there were people making money
aquí que había gente ganando dinero
on YouTube and I was with another
en en YouTube y estaba yo con otro con
guy with another guy with whom I did
otro chaval con el que yo hacía
collaborations who has a channel
colaboraciones que tiene un canal
too like mine big one eh she
también así como el mío grandecito eh se
came and she didn't stop being behind us
vino y no paraba de estar detrás nuestra
behind us and all that stuff that
detrás nuestra y todo el rollo ese que
for balls she with the with the sign no And
por huevo ella con la con el cartel no Y
the cover letter of I'm I don't know
la carta de presentación de soy no sé
who from Big Brother and I have a ton
quién de gran hermano y tengo un montón
of contacts Well, by balls she wanted to get involved, getting involved as
de contactos Pues por [__] quería ir
the ringleader and in the
metiendo metiendo la cabecilla y al
end she came out a little frog she came out a little frog
final pues salió ranilla salió ranilla
eh when we saw the feather duster we
eh cuando le vimos el plumero la la
left her aside I tried to leave her
dejamos de lado yo intenté dejarla de
aside I stopped talking to her but I didn't
lado la dejé de hablar pero no la
block her from anywhere or anything so that it was
bloqueé de ninguna parte ni nada para
clear that she was a person
que no pues se veía que era una persona
that was worth it you know and I left her
que la i valía sabes y la la dejé de
aside I left her aside I didn't answer her I didn't
lado la dejé de lado no le contestaba no
bring her to the Channel anymore and when she finally
la traía ya al Canal y cuando ya ella
gave up that she was not going to bring her
dio por perdido que ya no la iba a traer
to the Channel anymore, she started to  harass me and
más al Canal pues empezó a acosarme y y
every day she dedicates her existence to me
todos los días se dedica a mí su
all all but level
existencia todos todos pero nivel
e Well apart from the fact that she has had the
e Bueno aparte de que ha tenido la
lady is there whipping nu every day
señora esta ahí azotando nu todos días
using a cancer that they invented
utilizando un cáncer que se inventaron
such a level eh she is behind any
tal nivel eh va por detrás de cualquier
hater channel but not of telesalseo of the
canal hater pero no de telesalseo de los
topics that you see me but
temas que ustedes me veis sino a lo
maybe of the topics that I have with the
mejor de los temas que tengo yo con los
kids
chavales
mm she is trying to contact all the
mm va intentando contactar con todos los
channels that hate me to try to be a
canales que me odian para intentar ser
friend Look for Ally anyway she is
es amiga Buscar Aliado en fin es una
obsessed but well in a very
obsesionada pero bueno de una manera muy
strange way the truth and And well then she had for
rara la verdad y Y bueno pues tuvo para
me the episode that Defines her is the one of
mí el episodio que la Define es el de
the 240 she did a live okay where she
los 240 hizo un directo vale donde
raised money claiming that it was for
recaudó un dinero alegando que era para
cancer okay she asked for money for
el cáncer vale pidió dinero para
donations in a live she did a live
donaciones en un directo hizo un directo
and that the donations were going to cancer
y que las donaciones iban para el cáncer
and well they caught her that she hadn't given it
y bueno la pillaron que no la había dado
So she ran away she gave it the
Entonces se fue corriendo lo dio a la
same morning they caught her at 7
misma mañana que la pillaron a los 7
months 6s months she went running to
meses 6 s meses fue corriendo para
try to deceive people and tell them that she
intentar engañar la gente y decirle que
had given it cl or rather like it was
sí le había dado cl o sea en plan se le
seen let's go
vio vamos
the one of the pacha that is made
la de de la de la pacha que está hecha
See, I'm going to summarize it in four letters,
ve lo voy a resumir en cuatro letras
disgust. Look, Patrick, it's the same thing I
asco Mira Patrick es lo mismo que yo he
felt disgusted when I finished
sentido asco cuando he terminado de
listening to the space, disgust. Yes, why
escuchar el espacio asco Sí por qué
because they're saying logical things
porque están diciendo cosas lógicas
because they're saying logical things. Pepa
porque están diciendo cosas lógicas [__]
disgusts you, but what did you expect? They were going to
te da asco pero qu te esperabas que iban
say the same thing as the four you
a decir lo mismo que que los cuatro que
have in the
tienes en el
chat. No, no, no, no, just going around in circles. That's what has
chat no que no que no solamente vueltas
happened to many. I think that... well, it's
eso le ha pasado a muchos yo creo queus
talked about a lot. I commented on it here that there's
bueno eso se habla mucho lo comentó aquí
a lot of talk about Javid that he
que que que se habla mucho de javid que
stopped donating to her, that's why there's criticism. No, no, no, no,
dejó de donarle por eso la crtica no no
Javis. Oh, I'm not saying it, eh,
no no javis Oh no lo digo yo eh que no
I'm not talking about this, eh, it's what the
estoy hablando yo de esto eh es que lo
girl is saying. This is what I didn't
dice la chica esta eh el qué no lo he
understand. Wait, I'm going to
entendido espera lo voy a poner más
slow it down. Not only going around in circles. That's what has
lento Que no solamente vueltas eso le ha
happened to many. I think that... well,
pasado a muchos yo creo que acus bueno
this is talked about a lot. I think there was a
Esto se habla mucho cre lo comentó ayer
lot of talk about Javi yesterday that he
aquí que se habla mucho de Javi de que
stopped donating to her, that's why there's criticism. No, no, no,
dejó de donarle por eso la crítica no no
no, Javi. I
no no Javi
mean, the lady says there's a lot of talk about
O sea la señora dice se habla mucho de
Javi that Javi turned against
Javi de que Javi se puso en contra de
Loli. Because he stopped donating to her, I don't know what.
Loli Porque dejó de donarle no sé qué
Peppa.  She gets excited because she thinks she's
Peppa se emociona porque se cree que me
going to
van a
criticize me I'm not saying it eh I'm not
criticar No lo digo yo eh que no estoy
talking about that eh what this girl says
hablando Yo de eso eh que que lo dice la
eh selling yourself selling your
eh venderte vender tu
opinion not talking about what you want or
opinión no hablar de lo que tú quieres o
or not being sincere with with the rest of the
o no ser sincero con con con el resto de
people no no no no not only do you exist
gente no que no que no solamente existas
that has happened to many I think that
eso le ha pasado a muchos yo creo que
well that is talked about a lot I also think
bueno eso se habla mucho también creo
complain commented on it yesterday here that that there is a
quejo lo comentó ayer aquí que que que
lot of talk about Javi that he stopped
se habla mucho de Javi de que dejó de
donating to him that's why the criticism no no no no
donarle por eso la crítica no no no no
Javi stood up like a 10 and said Look Loli I'm not
Javi se plantó un 10 y dijo Mira Loli no
going to change my opinion because
voy a cambiado mi opinión porque porque
you don't like it if you don't like it there's
a ti no te gusta si no te gusta ahí tien
the
la
door Ah he believed he believed that the woman
puerta Ah se creía se creía que la mujer
was going to say the same mantra no ma'am no no no no what happens
iba a decir el mismo mantra no señora no
the things that have
no no no lo que tiene las cosas que han
happened in public and people have seen it
pasado en público y la gente lo ha visto
people have seen it I mean that
la gente lo ha visto o sea eso de que
here
aquí
Loli was the channel where he donated the most
Loli fue el canal en el que más donó
here Loli yes it is true that there have been
aquí Loli sí que es verdad que ha habido
times when he has made more or
veces que ha hecho donaciones más o
less large donations okay there have been live broadcasts in the
menos gordas vale habido directos en los
cadado 200 300  okay even a visa of 300 has been
cadado 200 300 vale incluso visum de 300
done okay But that has been two
ha hecho vale Pero eso ha sido dos meses
specific months or three specific months or
puntuales o tres meses puntuales o
even skipped, let's go if you want one day because
salteado incluso vamos si queréis un día
on YouTube that is already complicated, it is
es que en YouTube eso ya es complicado
complicated to check on YouTube
de es complicado de comprobar en YouTube
on YouTube I can't no, I don't know if you can
en YouTube no puedo no no sé si se puede
check only the super chat of
comprobar únicamente los super chat de
Loli huelta because that I don't know if it can be
Loli huelta es que eso no sé si se puede
checked because that is complicated but we
comprobar es que eso es complicado pero
could do that one day
eso lo podríamos hacer un día
eh we could do that one day I don't
eh eso lo podríamos hacer un día yo no
know if maybe searching by
sé si a lo mejor buscando por nombre de
username wait
usuario espérate
income statistics if I go
ingresos si me voy
to s
a
that if I go to super chat
que si me voy a superchat
Look if I go to super chat it appears
Mira si me voy a super chat me aparece
e by dates and such Look I mean if I go
e por fechas y tal Mira O sea si me voy
to super chat it appears maybe
a super chat me aparece a lo mejor
the
los
supers This is the money that they have
supers Este es el dinero que a mí me
given me in the month of Super chat you
llevan dado en el mes de Super chat
understand of course I understand that I can
entiendes claro Yo entiendo que puedo
put the month that you want but of course it doesn't
poner el mes que queráis pero claro no
differentiate by
me diferencia por
user it doesn't differentiate by users
usuario no me diferencia por usuarios
that would be very complicated to see the visas
eso sería muy complicado a ver los visum
yes I can see them obviously I search for
sí los puedo ver evidentemente Busco el
Loli's name and the visas I imagine
nombre de Loli y los visum me imagino
that I can see them but V you already know  I
que sí los puedo ver pero V ya te lo
say yes there have been three times
digo yo que sí que habido tres veces a
maybe two times in which
lo mejor dos veces en las que ha dado a
maybe a mink has given 200 out of 300 but
lo mejor un vison de 200 de 300 pero
outside outside I mean they haven't been they haven't been
fuera fuera O sea no han sido no han
three months Okay and Loli what
sido tres cu meses Vale y la Loli lo que
happens is that she believed that she had bought
pasa es que se creía que tenía comprada
the opinion and the things that could be
la opinión y de las cosas que se podían
talked about on the channels that gave money and
hablar en los canales que daba pasta y
here there was one that was the point it was
aquí hubo uno que fue ya el punto fue
when Marina fought with Marta Riesco
cuando Marina se peleó con Marta riesco
Loli was trying to stop that
Loli estaba intentando frenar ese
live because she gave superchat
directo porque diera ella superchat
Come on [ __ ] come on a person comes here no matter how
Vamos [__] vamos que viene aquí una
much money they have the
persona por mucho dinero que tenga el
channel doesn't
canal no lo
buy it the channel doesn't buy it because I
compra el canal no lo compra porque yo
don't depend on me my channels don't depend Look at
no dependo mis canales no dependen Mira
my channels the first thing they depend on is
mis canales de lo primero que dependen
me here money comes in because it's
es de mí aquí se ingresa dinero porque
me Okay so nobody can come here
soy yo Vale entonces aquí no puede venir
to buy the channel that's clear let's
nadie a comprar el canal eso está clar
go they have to give me let's see if they give me what I
vamos me tienen que dar a ver si me dan
know half a kilo maybe I'll
yo que sé medio kilo a lo mejor me lo
think about it and sell her one of the four okay
pienso y le vendo uno de los cuatro vale
but her the conflict was the day the
pero ella el conflicto fue el día el
conflict was the day and you can
conflicto fue el día y esto lo podéis
see this okay the conflict was the  day It's that
ver vale el conflicto fue el día Es que
this is proven but if it's that I've been
esto está probado pero si es que yo
saying that
llevo ya desde que llevan diciendo Esa
lie that I repeat the other day there was another
mentira que el otro día repito hubo otro
fool who was against me and
tonto que por estar en contra mí y
also a guy who doesn't even have that is
además un tío que no tiene ni que está
talking about me because he's
hablando de mí porque se supone que de
not supposed to talk about me and they sent me a
mí no tiene que hablar y me mandaron un
click from a fool saying it's not that
click de un tonto diciendo no es que
Loli what happens is that they gave her a hard time
Loli lo que pasa es que le dieron caña
Because she stopped donating and it's like
Porque dejó de canar de donar y es como
come show me the clips What's the
venga mostrarme los clips Cuál es la
cane and the crush that Anton also
caña y el machaque que anton también lo
said What is the what is the cli DM the
dijo Cuál es el cuál es el cli DM los
cli from day after day us
cli de un día tras día nosotros
crushing Loli that's a lie that this
machacando a Loli eso es una mentira que
lady invented to get her
se inventó la señora esta para sacarle
money here Loli donated that she was
la pasta aquí Loli donaba que estaba
fine okay a donor who was fine she was
bien vale una donadora que estaba bien
given special treatment Because she
se le daba un trato especial Porque
donated a lot I'm not going to deny that okay
donaba mucho eso no lo voy a negar vale
but it's like it's like for example who do I
pero es como es como por ejemplo quién
tell you well all those who donate a
te digo yo pues todos los que donan
lot, I mean imagine Orelvis that I think
mucho o sea imaginaros orelvis que creo
this one donated to me like 2000 members
que este me donó como 2000 miembros
between kids and telesalseo well if
entre chavalería Y telesalseo pues si
Orelvis tells me that or or I
orelvis me dice que o o me viene la
Orelvis's wife comes and tells me it's her
mujer de orelvis y me dice que es su
birthday. I'll sing her a tuna here,
cumpleaños le le canto aquí una tuna
of course, but you who have
lógico no pero ustedes los que tenéis
businesses, you who have bars. And don't you
negocio los que tenéis bares Y eso no le
add a little more ham and
echáis un poquito más de jamón y le
put a little more love to those who
ponéis un poquito más de cariño a los
come every day, I mean, it's
que vienen todos los días o sea es que
idiotic, the approach is
es de idiota el planteamiento
simply idiotic. But the thing about her
simplemente es idiota Pero eso de que
stopping donating here, she didn't
aquí dejó de donar ella aquí ella no
stop donating, she didn't stop donating here, she was
dejó de donar ella no dejó de donar aquí
kicked out. Come on, and it's not like she was kicked out.
aquí se le echó vamos y tampoco es que
Here, the door was
se le echara aquí tenía la puerta
always open until she started
abierta siempre hasta que empezó a
insulting and slandering people. And I always said so.
insultar y a calumniar y siempre lo dije
No, no, here, the door is open. She wasn't
No No aquí tiene la puerta abierta no se
kicked out either. What happened was that she came
le echó tampoco lo que pasa que vino
here complaining about that live show she
aquí como reclamando que el directo ese
did
que hizo
against Marina against Marta Riesco, okay,
contra Marina contra Marta riesco vale
F, you and Marina and
que F tú a día de hoy estamos Marina y
I are together with Marta Riesco. The other day,
yo juntos con Marta riesco el otro día
Marta spoke to me and said, whenever you want, I'll
Marta me habló y me dijo cuando quieras
upload it to your channel and I'll call her,
subo a tu canal y la voy a llamar
obviously, okay, but here, the day
evidentemente vale pero que aquí el día
of the conflict was Marina's thing, okay,
del conflicto fue lo lo de Marina vale
because Peppa was in the chat
porque Peppa estaba en el chat
applauding with  emojis that I have
aplaudiendo con emojis que lo tengo aquí
the
la
capture here and when she saw Loli she was
captura y cuando vio la Loli estaba
angry because Marta the next day
enfadada porque Marta al día siguiente
Peppa in her live went against
Peppa en su directo le llevó la contra a
Marina and supported Marta Because with Marta they
Marina y apoyó a Marta Porque con Marta
couldn't mess while they were
no se podían meter mientras que estaban
with Antonio David later when Marta
con Antonio David después cuando Marta
was no longer with Antonio David her
ya no estaba con Antonio David se le
head could be stomped under the ground which is
podía pisotear la cabeza bajo tierra que
where I also caught a lot Because
por ahí también pillé un montón Porque
I was on Marta's side and had to
yo estuve del lado de Marta y había que
be on the side of the mob that was on the side
est al lado de la turba que era al lado
of everyone messing with Marta okay there
de meterse todo el mundo con Marta vale
was also a nice time when you
que también hubo una epo guapa de
messed with Marta and humiliated her you
meterse toi con Marta y humillarla
know it gives us a lot of trouble when they
sabes que nos da mucha cosa cuando nos
humiliate us when they say things
humillan a nosotros cuando dicen cosas
about us but with Marta Marta
de nosotros pero a Marta a Marta estaba
everything was allowed and here we were the only ones
permitido todo y aquí fuimos los únicos
who were good with Marta and no, you see
que estuvimos bien con Marta y no verad
that I fell for it because it's good with Marta and they
que me cayo por est bien con Marta y me
told me with you'll see with time what it's going to
dijeron con el Ya verás con el tiempo la
give you here I've been for a year I
que te va a dar aquí estoy un año me
still get along well with Marta I call her from
sigo llevando bien con Marta la llamo de
time to time to see how she is she's
vez en cuando para ver cómo está ella me
going to come Marta is going to come this
ella va a venir Marta va a venir este me
had called me to
lo había llamado a mí a
Marta Marta is working well yes it
Marta Marta está trabajando pues sí que
is true that time has put
es verdad que el tiempo lo ha puesto
everything in its place
todo en su sitio
Marta is working and the masks are
Marta está trabajando y las caretas se
falling no no that same night in the chat
cayendo no no esa misma noche en el chat
libele was already positioned in the chat
ya se posicionó libele en el chat la
Peppa here in the telesalseo chat
Peppa aquí en el chat de telesalseo con
with 13000 viewers was
con 13000 espectadores estaba
applauding Marina and the pppa sent me a
aplaudiendo a Marina y me mandó un
WhatsApp that I have here that said tell
WhatsApp la pppa que lo tengo yo aquí
all this so that I would
que ponía dile a todo esto para que yo
mention her in public because when you
la mencionara en público porque cuando
send me a WhatsApp one thing
me mandas un Whatsapp una cosa que
you can say in the chat is so that I
puedes decir en el chat es para que yo
mention you to look for me to
te mencione para buscar que yo te
mention you in public and you think that with
mencione en público y te crees que con
that you are going to gain followers okay but she
eso vas a ganar seguidores vale pero me
sent me a super chat a WhatsApp
puso un super chat un WhatsApp
telling me about Marina It's true I
diciéndome lo de Marina Es verdad yo me
believe it something like that I don't remember okay and the
lo creo algo así no me acuerdo vale y al
next day she To please Loli
día siguiente ella Para complacer a Loli
did a live broadcast contradicting her and
hizo un directo llevándole la contrar y
there we said This girl is about what she is about
ahí ya dijimos Esta tía va de lo que va
This girl is dealing
Esta tía lo que tiene es un tejemaneje
with us to get us on
con nosotros para nosotros sacarnos por
one side and to get her on the other  the other
un lado y a la otra sacarle por el otro
to each their own and here with Loli here with
a cada uno los suyos y aquí a Loli aquí
Loli she was never given
a Loli no se le dio caña nunca me da
any stick I don't care I didn't notice if she left or not she left
igual yo no noté si se fue o no se fue
the truth here what happened was that
la verdad aquí lo que pasó que fue que
she started donating as if trying to
ella empezó a donar como intentando que
stop the live and we told her tirirí
pará el directo y le dijimos que tirirí
that I saw you come on that as if Loli tells me
que te vi vamos eso como si me lo dice
as if anyone tells me you
Loli como si me lo dice cualquiera me
understand me here the only one who could
entiendes aquí lo único que podía
complain that night about what was being
quejarse esa noche de lo que se estaba
said was Marta that Marta wanted to
diciendo era Marta que Marta quisiera
come in and answer Marina but a
entrar y contestar la Marina pero una
user because she becomes a fan of Antonia I saw
usuaria porque se haga fan de Antonia vi
and well And from there they started with
y bueno Y a partir de ahí empezaron con
the roll of inventing that that
el rollo de que de inventarse que esa
night Loli that she had sent superchat
noche Loli que había mandado superchat
here trust you the fascist la la the
aquí fíate tú la de facha la la las
ridiculous things that this lady has done to
ridiculeces que ha hecho esta señora por
crawl for Loli's money okay
arrastrarse por el dinero de Loli vale
Loli started saying that that night of the
la Loli empezó a decir que esa noche del
live with Marina against Marta that
directo con con Marina contra Marta esa
night I don't remember if it was a Tuesday or
noche no me acuerdo si fue un martes o
a Wednesday It seems like it was a Tuesday Uh
un miércoles Parece que fue un martes Eh
well Loli started saying that she
pues la Loli empezó a decir que ella
was having dinner in Granada that night with
estaba cenando en Granada esa noche con
Marta and Antonio David and  that Marta and
Marta y Antonio David y que Marta y
Antonio David didn't watch the live show and
Antonio David No vieron el directo y la
Peppa yes yes I have proof I've
Peppa sí sí yo tengo prueba yo lo he
seen it I've seen that they were having dinner
visto yo lo he visto que estaban cenando
together well Loli said that she saw me in
juntos bueno la Loli dijo que me vio en
Sierra Nevada that then the next day
Sierra Nevada que luego al día siguiente
she saw Mar and all that she has
vio a mar es que y todo eso esta le ha
gone along with every every nonsense
seguido el rollo a cada a cada payasada
that Huerta came up with that for me
que se inventaba el Huerta que yo para
I consider that she is a person that you shouldn't
mí Considero que es una persona que no
take into account what she says okay well you should
hay que tener en cuenta lo que diga vale
n't take into account it depends on
bueno no hay que tener en cuenta depende
what she says okay but you have to take her
que diga vale pero me hay que tomarla
very seriously okay for every nonsense that
muy en serio vale para cada payasada que
Loli came up with this was going behind
se inventaba Loli esta iba detrás
saying Yes yes I have proof I
diciendo Sí sí yo tengo prueba me
bet the Peppa channel she bet the
apuesto el canal Peppa se apostó el
channel that she would close it if what happened in Granada wasn't true
canal que lo cerraba si no era verdad lo
and days after that there was
granada y la y días después de eso hubo
a time that Loli went to get
una una vez que que la Loli fue a llamar
attention by donating in the live show that I did
atención donando en el directo que hice
about Marta the castle I told her Loli in
de Marta el castillo le dije Loli en
this live show you don't donate and I won't donate anymore I
este directo no se dona y ya no dono más
think I won't donate anymore okay But
creo que ya no dono más vale Pero
look at the sasca that she has eaten eh well it's that she
fijaros el sasca que se ha comido eh sea
is very short dude that has  happened
es que es muy corta tío eso le ha pasado
to many I think that is talked about
a muchos yo creo queus eso se habla
a lot, I think he commented yesterday here that they
mucho cre lo comentó ayer aquí que se
talk a lot about Ja That left
habla mucho de Ja Que
and Marta confirmed that Loli was not
dej y Marta confirmó que Loli no estaba
in Granada, she sent me audios and
en Granada me mandó a mí audios y
conversations with Loli about Loli saying
conversaciones con Loli de Loli diciendo
Marta that I have lied to defend you
Marta que yo he mentido para defenderte
how and Marta says to her what the [ __ ] Why the
cómo y le dice Marta para qué [__] En
[ __ ] are you defending me that you ate
qué [__] me defiendes que tú haya comido
with me in
conmigo en
Granada talk about that's why I criticize her no no no
Granada parle por eso la critic no no no
no Javi Oh I'm not saying it eh that I'm not
no Javi Oh no lo digo yo eh que no estoy
talking about that eh that
hablando Yo de eso eh que qu lo dice la
the girl says it
la chica esta
eh selling out selling your opinion or not not
eh venderte vender tu opinión o no no
talking about what you want we listen
hablar de lo que tú quieres escuchamos
well Peppa
bien Peppa
not being sincere with other people no that
no ser sincero con el resto de gente no
no only exas that has
que que no solamente exas eso le ha
happened to
pasado a
many people have commented here that they
muchos queus ha lo comenter aquí que se
talk a lot about Javi that he stopped
habla mucho de Javi de que dejó de
donating to her criticism no no no no Javi
donarle crítica no no no no Javi se
stood up one day and said Look Loli I'm not going to
plantó un día y dijo Mira Loli no voy a
change my opinion because because you don't
cambiar mi opinión porque porque a ti no
like it if you don't like it there's the
te gusta si no te gusta ahí tien la
door
puerta
amazing amazing the host you
alucinante alucinante la [__] que te
just
acabas de
got ridiculous  puy do man Don't do that
llevar ridículo puy hacer hombre No
man Don't do that
hagas eso hombre No hagas eso
man don't take it away
hombre no la quites
man people have seen people
hombre que la gente ha visto la gente la
have seen it if that has been experienced it's because they
ha visto si es que eso se ha vivido es
deny things that that have happened
que niegan cosas que que que han pasado
live man
en directo tío
amazing This seems amazing eh
alucinante Esto me parece alucinante eh
Diego and don't send people for
Diego y a no mandar a la gente por
mushrooms it seems like they are
champiñones que parece que están
picking
cogiendo setas
hallucinogenic mushrooms come on change pppa V change the
alucinogena venga cambia pppa V cambia
subject pppa
de tema pppa
of course laer seer everyone else
claro laer seer todos dems
open the door seg open but
abierta la puerta seg abierta pero
as long as you don't start defaming the
siempre y cuando no empezas a difamar en
moment he started yelling at us that if
el momento que empez a gritarnos que si
we are abusers if we are
somos maltratadores que si somos
harassers if we have stolen money from an
acosadores si hemos robado dinero de
account
cuenta
man well of course the door was closed
hombre pues claro que se cerró la puerta
because despite being a person who
porque a pesar de ser una persona que
donates a lot Dino and there is a lot to the Channel
dona much Dino y ay mucho al Canal
I don't think he's messing with Marina
Tampoco yo creo que se meene con Marina
Andal and Marina Andal is a very
andal y marina andal es una persona muy
loved person on the channel very loved by Javi
querida en el canal muy querida por Javi
very loved by all of Javi's followers
muy querida por todos los seguidores de
and and he was giving it to him because he didn't
Javi y y le estaba dando por porque no
like the Lie lie you have
le gustaban las Mentira mentira habéis
told another lie it is a space
dicho otra mentira más es un espacio
full of lies  a space full of
lleno de mentira un espacio lleno de
garbage That is uncertain It's more Marina
porquería Eso es incierto Es más Marina
ernal spoke with Loli privately
ernal se hablaba con Loli por privado
Loli has said it in some ration I
Loli lo ha dicho en alguna ración yo
never is a lie the only thing she said to
nunca es mentira lo único que le dijo a
Marina snal When she said that Anthony
Marina snal Cuando dijo que Anthony
David was afraid she said Anthony David is not
David tenía miedo dijo Anthony David no
afraid is doing So what happens that
miedo est haciendo Entonces qué pasa que
Javier chose chose but if on
Javier eligió eligió pero si es que
top of that look at the ridiculousness the
encima fíjate tú la ridiculez la
clown everything that he is doing
payasada todo lo que está haciendo
lady all this that you are making a
señora todo esto que está haciendo usted
fool of yourself and all the digital hella is because of because of
el ridículo y toda la hella digital es
having gone after a
por por por haber ido detrás de una
woman that you do not want nor would have
mujer a la que usted no quiere ni
ever been your friend and
hubiera sido su amiga jamás y
simply [ __ ] Ase the money that I
simplemente biche Ase el dinero que
donated you went after her to make an
donaba te fuiste a por ella a echarle
appointment on the phone and all this ridiculousness
hora por teléfono y todo este ridículo
is because of having read following the
es por haber leído siguiendo la
current to that lady for having for having
corriente a esa señora por haber por
read following all the lies
haber leído siguiendo todas las mentiras
that lady how is it going to be a lie If it has been
esa señora cómo va ha ser mentira Si se
lived If people have seen it have
ha vivido Si la gente la ha visto tiene
Eye is that it does not matter what you invent
Ojo es que da igual lo que te inventes
people have seen it have eyes and that's it
la gente la ha visto tiene ojos y ya
the guests would want and of
está los invitados quisieran y que por
course they were not sold that for me was
supuesto no se vendían eso para mí fue
to take off my hat that it was not sold
de quitar el sombrero que no se vendía
if they then came  here on the live
si luego han entrado aquí en el directo
Being with Loli to see if Loli
Estando yo con Loli para ver si Loli
Loli that the that Pepa was
Loli a que la a que la [__] te iba
behind you and what these other eloyes
detrás tuya y qué estos otras eloyes se
start to say but come on I don't know it seems that you
pone a decir pero vamos no sé parece que
are talking to 10 year old children they
estás hablando con niños de 10 años se
start to say when I did the debate
ponen a decir cuando yo hice el debate
with her on her channel that seems that
que con ella en su canal que parece que
for her it is a historical moment in her
para ella es un momento histórico de su
life and super important I don't know if she will have
vida y super importante no sé si tendrá
the debate put up high on TV not
el debate puesto en lo alto a la tele no
there but eh For me it was [ __ ] For
ahí pero eh Para mí fue una [__] Para
me it was like stopping to try to stop
mí fue como pararme a intentar frenar a
some bullies and ask them to leave me
unos acosadores y pedirles que me dejen
alone okay but for her it was the
en paz vale pero para ella fue el
moment of her life like more
momento de su vida como como más
important than communion okay they
importante que la comunión vale la se
start to give it as proof let's see [ __ ] yourself
ponen a a dar como prueba vamos a ver
[ __ ] yourself and find me all the clicks
cógete cógete y Búscame todos los clicks
where I have crushed Loli because Loli
donde yo he machacado a Loli porque Loli
stopped donating Prove it once and for all
dejé de donar Demuéstralo de una vez
come on As simple as Loli is
vamos Tan sencillo como que Loli está
sued that she takes the lawsuit and
demandada que coja la demanda y que
presents all those c Look I was
presente todos esos c Mira yo me estaba
defending myself from this you
defendiendo de esto
know what I'm telling you take it if she's
sabes lo que te digo que coja si lo
so clear about it  Damn, she takes the lawsuit
tiene tan claro [__] Que coja la demanda
and doesn't avoid it anymore,
y no la esquiva más
she takes the lawsuit And says, look at the
ella coge la demanda Y dice mira el
beating this youtuber did to me and
machaque que me hizo este youtuber y lo
presents it there and if I have beaten her
presenta ahí y si yo la he machacado
before the insults, she wins the
antes de los insultos de ella gana la
lawsuit, I will pay the
demanda le pago las
costs you know but I was going to say something and I let it
costas sabes pero iba a decir algo y se
slip because I was reading something Lili
me ha ido porque estaba leyendo a Lili
sent me, what was it?
mandado qué es lo que
Oh okay Yes, proof for her
era Ah vale Sí que una prueba para ella
that I wanted to get Loli back is that
de que yo quería recuperar a Loli es que
when Loli uploaded, do you remember in the
cuando Loli subió os acordáis en el
debate that I uploaded and I spoke calmly
debate que yo subí y le hablé con calma
to Loli that she got angry because Loli
a Loli que ella se enfadó porque Loli
when you take her and talk to her
cuando la coges y la la hablas
calmly Let her understand you, she told her
tranquilas Que ella te entienda le dijo
that I was right Peppa, you're
que yo tenía la razón Peppa tú estás
lying, but also if Javi is
mintiendo pero aparte si Javi te está
telling you to stop, each one goes their own
diciendo que pares para cada uno por su
way and Loli explained that Peppa
lado y la Loli expuso que la Peppa le
kicked her out, now on the phone she put a bunch
echaba ahora por teléfono puso un montón
of things and got angry with Loli she told her to
de cosas y se enfadó con Loli le dijo
go to hell Go to hell to her
iros a la [__] Vete a la [__] a su
friend because no, her friend is one, she saw her
amiga porque no su amiga es una la veía
like a wallet,
como un monedero
okay Well then she takes it out  a lot that I
vale Bueno pues ella saca mucho que yo
said live Loli honey
en el directo decía Loli cariño
listen to me
escúchame
Loli look look she says honey she says
Loli mira mira le dice cariño le dice
honey I'm telling her Here to María de la
cariño se lo digo Aquí a María de la
Cruz and to Pili and to I don't know who What's going on
cruz y a Pili y a no sé quién Qué pasa
I'm talking to an educated person
Estoy hablando con una persona con
Loli that Pepa was
educación Loli a que que la [__] iba
after you yes yes yes this the LoL
detrás tuya sí sí si esto la LoL lo
confirmed it they have the same the same
confirmó tienen el mismo el mismo
stupid speech of this no no no this is the
discurso estúpido de este no no no es el
speech that there is this is the
discurso que hay es la
reality money launderers there is more than one eh
realidad blanqueadores hay más de uno eh
but trust how little how little
pero es que fíate lo poco lo poco
stupid that speech is which is the
estúpido que es ese discurso que es lo
most logical let's see someone believes
más lógico vamos a ver alguien se cree
that this lady of the profile that she is
que esta señora del perfil que es
Knowing everything we know about her
Sabiendo ya todo lo que sabemos de ella
and all the handling that she does the
y todos los manejes que se trae lo de
240 all the things that she does someone
los 240 todas las cosas que hace alguien
believes that this woman has gone to
se cree que esta mujer ha ha ido a
become friends with Lolly randomly no Of
hacerse amiga de Lolly al azar no Por
course she hasn't become a friend a friend
supuesto que no se ha hecho amiga amiga
that is not a friend of come on Look if she is not a
que no es amiga de vamos Fíjate si no es
friend Look if she is not a friend that Loli
amiga Fíjate si no es amiga que Loli le
told her that the son was going to be a
dijo que el hijo iba a ser una
document forgery and Peppa didn't care
falsificación documental y la Peppa le
okay But you guys think it's
dio igual vale Pero ustedes creen que es
a random friendship  No man no Of
una amistad al azar No hombre no Por
course it's not a friendship because
supuesto que no es una amistad porque la
Peppa La bicha to Loli on our channel
la Peppa La bicha a Loli en el canal
yes Pablo Yes tomorrow we give tomorrow we give
sí Pablo Sí mañana damos mañana damos
another little direct surely Pablo has to
otro directillo seguro que Pablo tiene
reach 100000 tomorrow eh I'm going
que llegar mañana a los 100000 eh os voy
to forgive you that he didn't arrive today but
a perdonar que no haya llegado hoy pero
tomorrow we're going to give a bomb tomorrow
mañana vamos a dar una bomba mañana
we're going to give a bomb Yes Pablo I have I have a lot of
vamos a dar una bomba Sí Pablo tengo
things I have a lot of
tengo muchas cosas Tengo muchas cosas
new things my cell phone rang here while I was
nuevas me ha sonado el móvil aquí
live let's go but I have to
estando en directo vamos pero las tengo
see them then I'll watch it calmly when I
que ver luego la veré tranquilo cuando
finish the live broadcasts of the day but
termo los directos del día pero lo
we ally it Javi that you haven't told me
aliamos Javi que a m no me has dicho
darling well but let's see it's that if you
cariño pues pero a ver es que si usted
me yes you are here with me on a
me si usted estáis aquí conigo en el día
day to day basis I speak like this but even if it's an
a día yo hablo así pero aunque sea un
enemy even maybe in a
enemigo incluso a lo mejor en tono
sarcastic tone come on calm down darling come on honey
sarcástico como venga calma cariño venga
listen to me what I'm
corazón escúchame lo que te estoy
explaining to you I think it was something like that
explicando creo que fue algo así
okay clear dolores plex My poor thing let them
vale claro dolores plex Pobrecito mío
release it now I really like
que lo saquen ya a mí me cae muy bien
plex I know who he is let's see I know that
plex Yo sé quién es el a ver ya sé que
plex has
plex ha
announced I know that ple has announced his
anunciado Ya sé que ple ha anunciado su
series with shas but I know who he is
serie con el shas pero yo sé quién es el
next
siguiente
what happens is that of course he told me in
lo que pasa es que claro me lo contó en
confidence I'm not going to say it but I know
confianza no lo voy a decir pero yo sé
who is next after the
quién es el siguiente después del
showcast to do the series and
showcast en hacer la serie y le va a
people are going to love it they are going to freak out they are going to
encantar a la gente lo va a flipar lo va
freak out
a flipar a la
people are going to freak out but I'm not going to
gente lo va a flipar pero yo no lo voy a
say it because it's not an exclusive it's
decir porque no es una exclusiva es una
something that he told me in confidence he
cosa que me ha contado él en confianza
told me when I was in the
me la contó cuando estaba yo en el
sanctuary
santuario
Eh there are others who also don't have one
Eh hay otros que que tampoco tienen una
that follows the lane that follows the lane
que sigue el carril que sigue el carril
to the ball they do they do the Hello
ha la pelota le hacen le hacen la Hola
because when he enters the channel teola
porque cuando entra en el canal teola
300 400 500 that comes to you that's patri
300 400 500 que te viene eso es patri
Cari because here Loli doesn't do it I mean
Cari porque aquí Loli no lo hace o sea
YouTube I know that 30% of the Super chat
YouTube se que el 30% de los Super chat
eh all all there are many that are into in
eh todos todos hay muchos que le vana de
fact this group now of that before she
hecho este grupo ahora de de que antes
said that yes she was sick now
decía que sí que estaba enferma ahora la
excuse her like this trying to pull each one for
disculpar así intentando tirar cada uno
her for her channel to me that
para de ella para para su canal a mí eso
seems really ugly Hey how
sí que me parece feísimo Oye que
informed they are not to not watch YouTube
enteradas están no para no ver YouTube
there is some p space around here but Who
hay alguna p espacio por aquí pero Quién
said not to watch YouTube or  that they can't It's that
ha dicho que no vean YouTube o que no
this doesn't even make sense
pueden Es que esto no tiene ni sentido
the ridiculousness that
la ridicul que
[Music]
[Música]
people talk and that's what for me is
habla gente y eso es lo que para mí está
horrible and then you sell your opinion
horrible y después que vendas tu opinión
and your channel you sell everything for a
y tu canal lo vendas todo por una
donor that also selling your channel
donante eso también que vendas tu canal
and your opinion for an adante is
y tu opinión por una adante está
horrible and then you sell your opinion
horrible y después que vendas tu opinión
and your channel you sell everything for a
y tu canal lo vendas todo por una
donor that also selling your channel
donante eso también que vendas tu canal
and your opinion for an adante
y tu opinión por una adante
is that she is very burned but thinking about
es que está como muy ardida pero pensar
all that is that she is very burned with the
todo eso es que está muy ardida con la
opinion of these people from spacee and it's
opinión de esta gente del spacee y es
like
como
Peppa what did you expect what opinion did you
Peppa qué te esperabas que qué opinión
think people have about you
creías que tiene la gente sobre ti
Peppa
Peppa madre
my goodness we have always said that it
mía siempre hemos dicho que le
harmed her in fact it harms her to
perjudicaba de hecho le perjudica hasta
such an extent that in the superchat
hasta tal punto que en los superchat
because the Holi hueras to this day that
porque el Holi hueras a día de hoy que
her that her fandom and her I care a lot
su que su fandom y su me preocupo mucho
about saying fanatics please her fandom and
de decir fanáticas por favor su fandom y
her community are dedicated to saying in fact
su comunidad se dedican a decir de hecho
the other day I saw a t and someone
el otro día Vi un t y alguien a mí me
answered me that it has been a long time since
respondió que hace mucho tiempo que que
Antonio David has not dealt with Loli
Antonio David no se trata con Loli
huertas and  that lly huertas is already past
huertas y que lly huertas ya es pasado
for Antonio David
para Antonio David
and what Pepa
y qué [__]
what how informed you are of everything that is what
qué qué enteradas estáis de todo eso es
you have to say between the witch
lo que tienes que decir entre la brujita
the crumb the Lola the homeland very informed
la migaja la Lola la patria mu enterada
of
de
everything to this day she continues donating in
todoas a día de hoy sigue donando en
elav wait this is very good they
elav espera que este es muy bueno me
call me disgusting they
dicen asquerosísimo
continue to this day defending the
siguen a día de hoy defendiendo lo
indefensible because she continues giving money
indefendible porque sigue dando dinero
even when they have said that they were
incluso cuando han dicho que les daba
disgusted by Loli's money it's man Of course
asco el dinero de Loli es hombre Claro
because you said so beautiful that goes for you
porque tú lo dijiste guapa eso va por ti
because you
porque tú lo
said so how embarrassing the image that
dijiste qué vergüenza la imagen que
this lady has
tiene esta señora
eh whole that I told Loli
eh entera que yo se lo dije a Loli
even being her friend because I said
incluso siendo amiga de ella porque dije
Loli there is so much they have with your
Loli ya es tanto lo que tienen con tu
money that I no more than want your
dinero que yo no más que quiero tu
money I no more than want your money that
dinero yo n más que quiero tu dinero que
your money disgusts me coo because the other
ya tu dinero me da asco coo por el otro
day it didn't disgust you but apart from the fact that you
día no te dio asco pero aparte que se lo
told her being a friend your money disgusts me it
dijiste siendo amiga tu dinero me da
was before we fought and I told her
asco fue antes de pelearnos y se lo dije
but of course This is not a patri
yo pero claro Es que esto no es un patri
space this is a channel the replica of
espacio esto es un canal la réplica de
a channel the waves  that they are saying what
un canal las ondas que van diciendo lo
the other channel says totally this
que el otro canal dice totalmente esto
is a fandom you are a piece of
es un fandom sois un
[ __ ] Well go on,
un [__] Pues anda que no anda que no
there are people who criticize me
hay gente que me critican
there You would like to look like the ones from the
allí Ya quisieras tú parecerte a las del
patri space
patri espacio
Peppa
Peppa Ya quisieras
You would like but apart from that
tú pero aparte que
no eh
no eh
H
H
there neither Social Services that
ahí ya no tampoc Services sociales eso
is bad lasts because also you can't
es mal dura porque es que además tú no
confuse, I mean you can
puedes confundir o sea s puedes
confuse metastasis with a biopsy
confundir metástasis con una biopsia
but the moment you are
pero en el momento en el que eres
aware that you have confused you
consciente de que te has confundido
electrify and you don't let
electrificas y no dejas que se haga
such a Go and such a mess happen even
semejante Go y semejante lío incluso
inviting associations even
invitando a asociaciones incluso
inviting associations Exactly, I mean it's
invitando a asociaciones Exacto o sea
one thing if you make a mistake with the
una cosa es que tú te equivoques de
words But if you make a mistake
palabra Pero si tú te equivocas de
When someone corrects you you
palabra Cuando alguien te corrige lo
stop it okay But thanks taliu
frenas vale Pero gracias taliu
Thank you very much I'm waiting for the
Muchísimas gracias Estoy pendiente de la
time because right now I have to go with
hora porque ya mismo me tengo que ir con
trium okay to go it's almost 10
trium vale para irme son casi las 10
to go 15 20 minutes before to
para irme 15 20 minutillos antes para
prepare with him the live okay
prepararme con él el directo vale
[Music] that
[Música]
one thing if you make a mistake with the
que que una cosa que tú te equivoques de
words that doesn't count okay  obviously it's
palabra que no cuela vale evidentemente
an excuse Peppa always makes, she makes
es una excusa siempre pone la Peppa pone
excuses like when the kids catch her
excusa como cuando los niños Le cogen
not doing her homework, she makes some
sin hacer los deberes pone unas excusas
very ridiculous excuses. Thank you twi darling, but la
muy ridícula Gracias twi corazón pero la
la the thing is that Peppa, you have
la la cosa es que no Peppa tú te has
even invited people from
puesto hasta a invitar a gente de
associations against cancer, how disgusting,
asociaciones contra el cáncer qué asco
girl, how disgusting what you have done, eh how
tía qué asco lo que habéis hecho eh qué
disgusting and shameful, eh cancer, collecting
asco y la vergüenza eh cáncer haciendo
money etc.
colectas para donar dinero etcétera
etc. eh I have not collected money to
etcétera eh yo no he hecho colectas para
earn money, see, I don't think so, I don't think so,
ganar dinero ve no lo huevo no lo
everything that is donated from this
huevo todo lo que se done de este
live broadcast goes to
directo va para el
cancer, insults because it makes you angry, it
cáncer de de insulta porque te cabrea
hurts, insults because it makes you angry, show
que te duele insulta porque te cabrea
off as you are Peppa, yes we already
lúcete como tú eres Peppa si ya te
know what you are like, we have been seeing you for two years, you are the
sabemos cómo eres llevamos dos años
same, this is Elenita
sois iguales sois esto es Elenita
Patricia espacio
Patricia espacio
puno Yes, it is what it seems to me that we have
puno Sí es que es lo que me parece que
reached those limits that the ball
sol llegar a esos límites de que la bola
is so enormous that even
es tan enorme que incluso se meten
associations get involved and sick people get involved and relatives
asociaciones y se meten enfermos y se
of sick people get involved, relatives of
meten parientes de enfermos parientes de
sick people, of course I brought the
enfermo claro yo traje al
guy, shame how far these
tío verguenza hasta dónde llegan esta
people go  where do you get because what they are
gente hasta dónde llegas tú porque lo
saying is true being a
que están diciendo es verdad ser un
fandom of a YouTube channel in that in
fandom de un canal de YouTube en esa en
that situation the c unfortunately is one that
esa situación el c por desgracia es una
I was afraid to say to 100% of the
al quea yo me teía decir al 100% de los
Spanish because if it is not a family of your
españoles porque si no es una familia
own everyone knows someone
propia todo el mundo conocemos a alguien
so eh letting something
entonces eh dejar que se juegue con algo
like that be played with disgusts me the same
como eso a mí me provoca asco el mismo
disgust that you are causing me and that you
asco que me estás provocando tú y que me
have caused me when I was listening to you
Has provocado cuando yo te escuchaba
this space patri you disgust me
este espcio patri me produces asco
so much I don't know if I'm going to return it
muchísimo asco no sé si voy a devolver
now or I'm going to return it
ahora o voy a devolver más
later what else
tarde qué má
Pili one more me qua come on disgusting they
Pili uno más me qua venga asquerosísimo
continue to this day defending the
siguen a día de hoy defendiendo lo
indefensible because he continues giving money
indefendible porque l sigue dando dinero
even when they have said that they were
incluso cuando han dicho que les daba
disgusted by
asco el dinero de
Lori's money pat don't you understand that I told
Lori pat no te enteras que yo se lo dije
LoL even being a friend Ah but you're
a LoL incluso siendo amiga Ah pero te
wrong here you sent me the
equivocas aquí me has mandado el
same sea is telling me Pili Well they
mismo sea me está diciendo Pili Bueno me
show me this clip that Pili is not here
ponen este clip que Pili no está aquí
now no Pili you are there well it doesn't matter let's
ahora no Pili tú está ahí bueno da igual
go to the channel I'm going to
vamos a el canal Voy a
see it that
verlo que
Loli has come in by
que Loli ha entrado por
phone come on see the defense  what did
teléfono venga ver la defensa que te ha
Loli do to you and Alberto uploaded it at 3 in
hecho Loli y subió mi Alberto a las 3 de
the
la
morning he
mañana los
deleted them Look what a load of money eh again
elimino Mira qué asco de dinero eh otra
well this is what there is Well now I
vez pues esto es lo que hay Bueno ahora
removed it But this is still there hit
lo he quitado Pero esto sigue ahí dale
me they're going to put me Oh How are they
que te pego me van a poner Ay Cómo me
going to put me
van a poner
eh this space is going to bring me to my
eh el espacio este me va a traer a mí
tail but I couldn't hold back putting
cola pero es que no podía aguantar de
it on because I was freaked out
ponérmelo porque me he quedado flipa
come on I was freaked out it's here Loli
venga se quedado flipa ya está aquí Loli
Huerta come on Good afternoon
Huerta venga Buenas tardes
Loli Hello how are you Wait what am I going to put on
Loli Hola qué tal Espérate que te pongo
you what I had removed eh
que te había quitado eh
nothing have you seen it haven't you been able to
nada lo hais visto no tú lo has podido
put it on Yes of course
poner Sí claro
why But because you're in that Stream
porque Pero porque tú estás en el Stream
yar and you went to the point but
yar ese y te has ido al puntito pero
ask chat if it stayed
pregúntale a chat si si se ha quedado
there or left immediately
ahí o se ha ido al momento
eh Wait The question is if they have
eh Espérate La pregunta es si ellos han
seen the super chat question is if it hasn't
visto el super chat pregunta es si no ha
been
sido
deleted the one who can delete it from the
eliminado el que puede eliminarlo de
screen is the person who
pantalla es ser la propia persona que lo
does it Ah friend I didn't know that you can
hace Ah amiga Eso no lo sabía yo puedes
delete it yourself you can d have that
eliminarlo tú solo se puede a d tienen
those of the humiliation of the 240 of
que los de la humillación de los 240 de
Irene people who suffer and suffer
Irene personas que lo sufren y padecen
shame
verguenza
climbs Exactly the funny little thing with the 240
trepa Exacto el cachon deito con los 240
laughing at what he
riéndose de lo que
did is that he already believes that
hizo es que ya se cree que esto se le va
people are going to forget this and this is not
a olvidar a la gente y esto no esta eres
you on the Internet Peppa you wanted to be a
tú en Internet Peppa tú querías ser
youtuber well your face can be seen this
youtuber tú pues se te ve tu cara esto
is like what happened to you in Big Brother
es como lo que te pasó en gran hermano
It has happened to him Exactly the same thing you
Es que le ha pasado Exactamente lo mismo
see people who earn money you think it is
ves a gente que gana dinero crees que es
easy money quickly and you think that such
un dinero fácil rápido y crees que tal
but of course you do not take into account that
pero claro no tienes en cuenta que sale
your true self comes out you get into the
tu verdadero yo te metes en la casa de
Big Brother house What did MC Mila tell you that you
gran hermano Qué te dijo MC Mila que
were a bad person a
eras una persona mala lianta
liar you are inside the
mentirosa estás dentro de la casa de
Big Brother house they are recording you things
gran hermano te están grabando las cosas
happen live things happen
pasan en directo las cosas pasan en
live in front of a camera you
directo encima delante de una cámara
cannot then tell your version and lie
no puedes luego contar tu versión y liar
because people are watching it and here the
porque la gente lo está viendo y aquí ha
same thing has happened you have gone to a person, I
pasado lo mismo estás ido a una persona
mean you have
o sea te has
gone to other people's channels and you have been
ido a los canales de otra gente y te has
noticing the people who give money
ido fijando en la gente que da dinero
writing down in a notebook who gives money you
apuntando en una libreta quién da dinero
have looked for them on Instagram and you have
la has buscado por Instagram y has
become friends with them
cogido amistad con ella
friendship  the house side for Loli's money
amistad la cas lado por el dinero de
to get the money out of her so she would
Loli para sacarle el dinero para que te
give you as much as possible that if they
lo diera todo lo posible que si te
put the videos in Yellow that if they
ponían los vídeos en Amarillo que si te
put the videos in
ponían los vídeos
purple then then the issue of the Can has
morados luego luego el tema del Can ha
been and more the mess the mess No no it's that
sido y más el lío el lío No no es que
Javi gave her money and since she didn't give it to him anymore he messed
Javi le daba dinero y como ya no le daba
with her and then I stood up
por se metía con ella y entonces yo daba
for her Peppa is talking if I
la cara por ella está hablando Peppa si
have everything recorded here and I have everything
tengo aquí todo grabado y lo tengo todo
saved to sue you if I have all
guardado para demandarte si tengo todos
your live shows saying with a
los directos tuyos diciendo con la cara
sad bitter face well ask
todo triste amarg pues preguntarle a
Javi Why doesn't he mention me it's that Javi ignores me it's that
Javi Por qué no me menciona es que Javi
Jai doesn't me Of
pasa de m es que Jai no me
course Javi had already seen through you And Javi would
Claro que Javi ya te había calado Y Javi
n't let you in here you
aquí no te dejaba
know and all this in front of a
entrar sabes y todo esto delante una
camera and now you're surprised that in a
cámara y ahora te sorprende de que en un
space some ladies with whom I have
space unas señoras con las que no tengo
nothing because the only one there that I
nada porque yo con la única de ahí que
've spoken with is Patrick who no I'm not
he hablado es con Patrick que no no
friends but I've spoken
tengo una amistad pero he hablado
a few times you know what I mean I mean I've
algunas veces me entiendes o sea vamos
spoken I've spoken many times with
he hablado he hablado muchas veces con
Patrick Okay and but we're not friends we don't
Patrick Vale y pero no somos amigos no
tell each other secrets I mean like you
nos contamos secretos o sea en plan
know I don't send her  in fact there
sabes no la mando de hecho muchas veces
are often many of her friends who mess
hay muchas amigas suyas que se meten
with me no Lola I remember that she messed
conmigo no Lola recuerdo yo que se metía
with me a lot Majo I don't think it's much like
mucho conmigo Majo creo que no es mucho
me eh I think they are people who
de mí eh Me suena que son gente que me
give me a hard time eh What happens is that of course they are not
dan cañita eh Lo que pasa que claro no
going to agree with you on something that
te van a dar la razón en una cosa que ha
happened in public No no that thing that
pasado en público No no eso de que que
you made up that Javi I don't know
tú te has inventado de que Javi No sé
what no the thing about Peppa is crazy but the thing
qué no lo de Peppa es de traca pero lo
about Loli who continues to defend her and
de Loli que sigue defendiéndola y
support her is already psychological but it does
apoyándola ya es de psicólogo pero es
n't make any sense Mercedes
que no tiene sentido ninguno Mercedes
Milani will remember Peppa Well yes
milani se acordará de la Peppa Bueno sí
maybe yes I don't know let's see about the
a lo mejor sí no lo sé a ver de los
contestants if she will remember but it does
concursantes si se acordará pero que es
n't make any sense they have already
que no tiene sentido ninguno que ya han
said that Loli made it up that Loli
dicho que Loli se lo inventó que la
herself told her that come on there
propia Loli le ha dicho que ya vamos no
was no need for me to say it that it was
hací falta que lo diga que ya era
enough Javi you are in five live shows
suficiente Javi estás en cinco directos
really that it was more than
serio que ya era más que
enough When she said that they had
suficiente Cuando decía que le habían
given her boobs at the same time that the
puesto tetas a la vez que el
lung come on I'll take you away I'll take away your lung and
pulmón venga te quito te quito pulmón y
give you boobs and for TR late dancing with a dove is
te pongo teta y por TR tarde bailar con
that already with that was
una paloma es que ya ya con eso era
enough I didn't need more but anyway
suficiente no me hacía falta más pero
in case there was anyone who had
bueno por si había alguien que tenía
doubts she already said it and she already said it
dudas ya la ha dicho ella y ya lo dijo
in an audio What's the point now what's the point now what's the point of
de Troya en un audio A qué viene ahora a
saying
qué viene ahora a qué viene ahora decir
again that no that she did have it that it doesn't make
otra vez que no que si lo tuvo que no
any sense at all well they're not
tiene sentido ninguno bueno no están
saying that she did have it eh They're not
diciendo que si lo tuvo eh No están
saying that she did have it Well if you
diciendo que si lo tuvo Pues si os dais
notice Peppa is saying that she used a
cuenta la Peppa lo que está diciendo es
mistake
que se equivocó de
the ard Troy is already defending
palabra el ard Troy ya está defendiendo
that she did have it I mean if you
que sí lo tuvo la O sea si os dais
notice each one is saying something
cuenta cada uno está diciendo una cosa
[ __ ] I hadn't thought of that they are
[__] no había caído en eso la están
defending her but whatever each one with
defendiendo pero como sea cada uno con
their own thing because Peppa has already said
su movida porque la Peppa ya ha dicho
that she used a mistake if you're saying that she used a mistake she
que se equivocó de palabras si estás
's admitting that she didn't have it Of course,
está reconociendo que no lo tuvo Claro
of course, of course, damn it hadn't occurred
claro claro claro [__] no había caído
to me Lili of course the pppa has already said
en eso Lili claro la pppa ya ha dicho
that she used a mistake the ard of
que se equivocó de palabra el ard de
Troy Ana Cotilla Elton Joe that I have
Troya la Ana Cotilla el Elton Joe que lo
also heard in one click they have
he escuchado también en un click han
put it on Twitter Of course,
puesto en Twitter Claro
of course that's what they are saying that if they believe her
claro eso están diciendo que si la creen
But if  Peppa is telling you no
Pero si te está diciendo la Peppa que no
Peppa is telling you no that she didn't have it
la Peppa te está diciendo que no que no
that they used the wrong word and
lo tuvo que se equivocaron de palabra y
there she is with Loli on the phone which is what she
ahí está con Loli en teléfono que es lo
is defending the anotia and the
que está defendiendo las anotia y los
others who don't even understand each other that they
otros que no se entienden ni ellos que
want Loli's money damn you do a
quieren el dinero de Loli [__] que le
super chat with her and she says otherwise I'm
hagáis super chat y dice lo contrario yo
going to the an Cotilla tomorrow I will do
voy mañana a la an Cotilla le hago
four super chat with her and she says
cuatro super chat y te dice lo
otherwise delete by the person who
contrario eliminar por la persona que
does
hace
the super chat I didn't know that Ah Well
e el super chat eso no lo sabía yo Ah
I do but look at that forat space to
Pues yo sí pero mira eso paraat espacio
go learning izas make at least
ir aprendiendo izas hacer por lo menos
one euro and and try it okay that's it
un eurito y y probarlo vale eso eso es
you have confused
te has confundido
me no Javi who already says that he
conmigo no Javi que ya dice que sí lo
had it again but self-criticism if he is
tuvo otra vez pero autocrítica si está
saying that he used the wrong
diciendo que se ha equivocado de
word he is saying that he didn't have it
palabras está diciendo que no lo tuvo
if he is saying that he used the wrong
si está diciendo que se ha equivocado de
word he is saying that he didn't
palabra está diciendo que no lo
have it because then no he is not defending that he used the wrong
tuvo porque entonces no no defiende que
word he would
palabra
not say
no diría
eh that Loli was wrong when she said
eh que Loli se ha equivocado al decir
that s I have no [ __ ] idea I have no
que s no tengo ni [__] idea no tengo ni
[ __ ] idea the
[__] idea la
truth everywhere everywhere
verdad en todos lados en todos lados
Javi Javi every day already but well let's
Javi Javi todos los días ya pero bueno a
see  everywhere Jai every
ver en todos lados Jai todos los
day but that's logical not who are you going to
días pero eso Es lógico no de quién van
talk about if not guys are the come on
a hablar si no chicos son las venga
let's see a little more here what's going on
vamos a ver un poco más aquí que va de
nap because it's
siesta porque es
short Well I was to answer one
corto Pues yo era para contestarle una
of the things to one of the things have already been
de las cosas a una de las cositas ya
answered says Lili she they what they
contestadas dice Lili ella ellas lo que
defend is that Loli had cancer
defienden es que Loli tuvo cáncer hace
years ago as if we cared about the
año como si nos importase el historial
medical history of the past before using the
médico del pasado antes de usar la
supposed illness against you let's
supuesta enfermedad en tu contra vamos a
see what they say that I don't know if it will be
ver s que dicen que yo ya no sé si será
true Of course because I understand that it's not
verdad Claro porque yo entiendo que
true either the one from the past, I don't [ __ ]' know that, I don't
tampoco verdad el del pasado no [__]
know that, I don't know if the one
eso no lo sé eso no lo sé no sé si el
from the past because of course when the
del pasado porque claro cuando habla la
Sister speaks she says that she never had cancer
Hermana dice que nunca tuvo cáncer
So when the Sister says never
Entonces cuando la Hermana dice nunca
had No, we know the one from the past if it
tuvo No eso lo sabemos el del pasado si
's true or a lie because the one from the
es verdad o es mentira porque el del
past that is clearly not the topic because the
pasado ese claro no es el tema porque el
topic
tema
is the topic is the current one because it's the one
es el tema es el el actual porque es el
that they use to whip us in
que ellas utilizan para azotar noos en
the click that we've seen these days that
los clic que hemos visto estos días que
look they are Taking advantage of the fact that I'm in the
mira están Aprovechando que estoy en el
hospital I'm taking advantage of the fact that I'm
hospital Estoy aprovechando que estoy
weak to attack me and he crushes me every
débil para atacarme y me machaca cada
time I'm  admitted I mean, how disgusting
vez que estoy ingresada O sea qué asco
what they did
lo que hicieron
eh how disgusting what they did eh Sure,
eh qué asco lo que hicieron eh Claro
but the relative said
pero el familiar dijo que
never the relative the sister said
nunca el familiar la hermana dijo que
never but when we say never we
nunca pero cuando decimos nunca lo
understand it as never it's not
entendemos como nunca no se está
referring to the last thing because you
refiriendo a lo último porquees tú
can use better no never
puedes utilizar a mejor no nunca lo ha
had it but in the sense of the last It's
tenido pero en el sentido de lo último
not going Javi You don't stop working today and
No anda Javi No paras de currar hoy y
what day do I stop samor and what day
qué día paro samor y qué día
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
stop I'm going I'm going to well come on
paro me voy que voy a bueno venga a
say something else I'm going to go get
decir algo más que me voy a ir a
ready with trib on live Damn he
preparar con trib en el directo [__] me
's talking to me Over here tuyupa's boyfriend
está hablando Ya por aquí el novio de
nobody has taken anything from me Super chat watch out watch out
nadie me ha quitado nada de Super chat
today we're going to have a
ojo que ojo que hoy vamos a tener una
very powerful exclusive eh on the
exclusiva muy potente eh en el canal
main channel the
principal la
sentence the exclusive sentence of Daniel Sancho has
sentencia la sentencia de Daniel Sancho
n't come out anywhere yet
exclusiva no ha salido todavía ninguna
no maybe they got
parte no a lo mejor se nos han
ahead of us during the afternoon but I think
adelantado durante la tarde pero creo
not but I think
no pero creo que
not every time I feel like it I have it I have it
no siempre que me da la gana los la
Elena Now we're going over
tengo la tengo Elena Ahora nos vamos
there to the main channel a bomb
para allá para el principal una bomba
eh it's a
eh es una
bomb it's a bomb it's a bomb I'm going to
bomba es una bomba es una bomba me voy a
go get ready now  with trium okay I'm
ir a prepararlo ya con trium vale que
going to comment because tuju has already
voy a comentar porque tuju ya la ha
read it it's in English It's in English not
leído está en inglés Está en inglés no
in Thai and trium is there poor thing
en tailandés y trium está el pobre ahí
struggling he's been there for 4 hours
luchando que lleva ya 4 horas ahí
trying to translate I don't know what I don't know
intentando Traducir no sé qué no sé
how much and he wrote to me he told me
cuánto y me me ha escrito me ha dicho
that he found something that we didn't
que ha encontrado algun cosilla que no
know about Well in 15 minutes let's go
sabíamos a Pues dentro de 15 minutos
in fact I'm going to do a
vamos es que de hecho os voy a hacer una
Ray for the main channel so that
Ray para el canal principal para que
you're there okay so don't touch
estéis allí ya vale o sea que no toquéis
anything You're going to go there when I close
nada Vais a caer allí cuando yo cierre
the
el
live You're going to go there when I
directo Vais a caer allí cuando yo
close the live okay And and don't touch
cierre el directo vale Y y no toquéis
anything okay go to the bathroom prepare dinner
nada vale iros al baño preparar la cena
or whatever okay And we'll start in 15
o lo que sea vale Y empezaremos en 15
minutes more or less 15 minutes
minutillos más o menos 15 minut
okay So don't touch anything I'm going to
vale Así que no toquéis nada voy a
cut You're going to go there and you guys are going to
cortar Vais a caer allí y ustedes Vais a
grab something and we're going over there it's
[__] algo y y nos vamos para allá es
very strong what we have eh they've already given him
muy fuerte lo que tenemos eh le han dado
the sentence but the whole thing I don't think they've
ya la sentencia pero entera No creo que
given any program
hayan dado ningún programa
eh Let's see
eh A ver
Yes yes it has already been in the media it has
Sí sí ha salido ya en los
been in the media it has
medios ha salido ha salido en los medios
been in the media what  It happens that it
ha salido en los medio Lo que pasa que
is true that I think it is not the whole thing,
sí que es verdad que creo que entera no
eh? It is almost 50 pages. But well, we are
eh Son casi 50 páginas Pero bueno nos
going there, we are going there,
vamos para allá nos vamos para allá
guys, a kiss, I will see you there, okay, in the
chicos un beso os veo allí vale en el
main page.
principal